<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>RSS</title>
    <link>https://rssfeedbhel.000webhostapp.com</link>
    <description>Combined RSS</description>
    <lastBuildDate>1562747509</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Sunil Gavaskar: Sachin Tendulkar Leads Wishes On Former India Captain's 70th Birthday]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/cricket/happy-birthday-sunil-gavaskar-sachin-tendulkar-leads-wishes-on-former-india-captains-70th-birthday-2067207]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunil Gavaskar was the first batsman to score 10,000 Test runs and was one of the greatest opening batsmen in the business.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562747144]]></pubDate>
    <image><url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/b4lkvjeg_sunil-gavaskar-twitter_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url></image></item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Disney Defends Black Actress In And As 'The Little Mermaid']]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/after-protests-over-black-ariel-disney-defends-casting-halle-bailey-in-and-as-the-little-mermaid-2067201]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cast news prompted protests from some who launched hashtags such as #NotMyAriel and #NotMyMermaid]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/b01r24bg_the-little-mermaid-wp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746614]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[TS Inter Supply Result Date To Be Announced Tomorrow]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/education/ts-inter-supply-result-2019-date-update-2067200]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[TS Inter Supply results are expected to be published on portals affiliated with the Board including tsbie.cgg.gov.in, bie.telangana.gov.in, exam.bie.telangana.gov.in and results.cgg.gov.in.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/nv6nle5g_result_625x300_25_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746529]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi-Final Live Score, World Cup 2019: India Look To Wrap New Zealand Amid Rain Threat]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-reserve-day-live-cricket-score-match-updates-2067180]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi-final Live Score, 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup: India-New Zealand clash was moved to the reserve day due to rain.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746422]]></pubDate>
    <image><url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/4ifqoq1g_india-vs-new-zealand-twitter_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url></image></item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rebel Lawmakers Approach Top Court, Say Speaker Has "Abandoned Duty"]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/karnataka-crisis-rebel-lawmakers-move-supreme-court-allege-speaker-abandoned-constitutional-duty-2067199]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Senior advocate Mukul Rohatgi appeared in court on behalf of the rebel legislators. The former Attorney-General asked that the matter be heard urgently but the court declined to do so. The matter will...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/o2fru42g_karnataka-rebel-lawmakers-renaissance-hotel-ndtv_650x400_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746274]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA["Keep Running," Anand Mahindra Tells Dutee Chand After Historic Win]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/offbeat/blessed-says-dutee-chand-as-anand-mahindra-hails-her-historic-win-2067198]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dutee Chand became the first Indian to clinch a gold medal at World Universiade after she won the 100m dash event held in Naples, Italy. The victory led to a lot of congratulatory messages on social...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/2mkslvao_dutee-chand-twitter_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746224]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[OnePlus Launcher Update Brings Password Support for Private Apps]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/apps/news/oneplus-launcher-update-hidden-space-password-setting-support-2067197]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Hidden Space feature essentially allows you to keep private apps in a place where no one can see, even if they are browsing through your phone.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/onepluslauncher_main1_1562746308524.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746176]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Karnataka Crisis Rocks Rajya Sabha, House Adjourned Till 2 pm]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/karnataka-crisis-rocks-rajya-sabha-house-adjourned-till-2-pm-2067194]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Opposition Congress members today again disrupted proceedings in Rajya Sabha over the Karnataka crisis and accused the BJP of trying to destabilise the party's coalition government in the state.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-01/mfpcbhjc_venkaiah-naidu-rajya-sabha-pti_625x300_02_January_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562746016]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Redmi Note 7 Pro Now on Open Sale Till July 12 on Flipkart, Mi.com]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/redmi-note-7-pro-open-sale-till-july-12-flipkart-mi-com-offers-price-in-india-specifications-2067192]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Xiaomi announced this Redmi Note 7 Pro open sale to celebrate the 15 million worldwide shipment milestone.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/redmi_note_7_pro_1558444051612.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562745968]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[IND vs NZ semi-final: Manchester weather updates]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/manchester-weather-updates-advantage-india-with-semi-final-to-be-completed-on-reserve-day/articleshow/70153705.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As per the rain rules of the International Cricket Council (ICC), if there is no play possible on the reserve match day and no winner is determined, the higher placed team from the league stage will progress to the final.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562745830]]></pubDate>
    <image><url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153872,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1330001,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url></image></item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Barrier In Wrong Place Blamed For Dubai Bus Crash That Killed 12 Indians]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/indians-abroad/barrier-in-wrong-place-blamed-for-dubai-bus-crash-that-killed-12-indians-2067188]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lawyers of the Omani bus driver, who rammed the vehicle into a height barrier in Dubai that killed 17 people including 12 Indians, have told a UAE court that the restriction bar violated the GCC...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/34kcb16g_dubai-bus-crash_625x300_07_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562745733]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Drought forces doctors to buy water for surgery]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/politics-and-nation/indias-worsening-drought-is-forcing-doctors-to-buy-water-for-surgery/articleshow/70155777.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[By Archana Chaudhary and Shivani KumaresanAlong with other doctors in Indian cities facing unprecedented water shortages, TN Ravisankar in Chennai is praying for rain — and soon.Treating patients will "depend on God’s mercy" if water supplies in India’s fourth-largest metropolis aren’t replenished shortly, said Ravisankar, the chairman of Sudar hospitals, a chain of four clinics with 150 beds. Piped water at his hospitals has already dried up, and even the more expensive water trucks he now relies on may be unavailable soon in Tamil Nadu."The cost escalation will have to be passed on to patients, who will have to spend more," Ravisankar said. "If the situation continues, after a month we won’t be able to serve patients."Failed rains last year and delays in this year’s annual monsoon have left nearly half of India facing drought-like conditions, according to the South Asia Drought Monitor. Tamil Nadu is trapped in a “severe dry” cycle along with other states like Karnataka, Andhra Pradesh and Maharashtra.Up north, India’s capital New Delhi has recorded the worst monsoon delay in 45 years. With piped water supply available to less than a fifth of Delhi homes, political parties have traded barbs with the state government over the lack of planning for water-truck supplies to large swathes of the city.As the impact of climate change worsens, water is shaping up to be a serious economic risk in Asia’s third-largest economy. Desertification, land degradation and drought cost India about 2.54% of gross domestic product in 2014-15, according to a study last year by India’s environment ministry.India has witnessed widespread droughts in four of the past five years, and the government forecasts that per head availability of water will fall by 35% next year from 2001 levels. Hospitals, which rely on water for sanitation and preventing infections, are suffering as the cost of water rises.The administration of Prime Minister Narendra Modi, who promised an ambitious healthcare expansion ahead of his re-election in May, announced a water conservation awareness program on July 1. Yet it’s unclear if the measures will be enough to ensure a steady supply of clean water.“Not many are informed about just how big the dangers are,” said Arivudai Nambi Appadurai, head of India adaption strategy at the World Resources Institute, a Washington-based group that researches ways to protect the environment. “The quality of water being bought even by homes in drought-struck areas has caused allergies, sending more patients to local hospitals in places like Chennai.”Almost all of Chennai’s hospitals are now completely dependent on the more than 5,000 privately-owned tankers that ferry water around the city every day, according to N. Nijalingam, president of the Tamil Nadu Private Water Tanker Lorry Owners’ Association. But it’s becoming tougher to source water even from 100 kilometers (62 miles) away, he said.“If the situation continues, after a month we won’t be able to supply water even to the people who can pay a huge sum for a tanker of water,” he said.The price of a 12,000-liter water truck soared from Rs 1,200 in April to as high as Rs 6,000 since shortages began, The News Minute website reported. Smaller nursing homes and clinics in Chennai, a medical tourism hub, have been hit harder than larger hospitals that have more money, according to Balaji Venu Gopal, a vascular surgeon at Apollo Hospitals in Chennai.“Nobody has come out openly to raise the issue and seek government support so far,” said Venu Gopal. “But the crisis is definitely cutting the profit margin of the medical industry.”The water shortages risk further hurting the already struggling state-run health system. India spends only around 1% of GDP on healthcare, and aims to increase it to 2.5% by 2025. By comparison, nations whose entire populations have access to health services spend as much as 6% of GDP on insurance and healthcare, according to the World Health Organization.“The pressure on us rises every time there’s a drought,” said Ashok Thorat, chief medical officer at a state-run hospital in Beed, Maharashtra. “More people turn up at our government hospital because private clinics have to pay more to buy water and pass on costs to patients. We can arrange at least some free water from the municipal corporation, but even that has limits.”Thorat says his hospital, which serves a town of 1,47,000 people about 380 kilometers east of Mumbai, had to buy two water trucks of about 10,000 liters each in May. His 500-bed hospital needed more trucks in June after rains failed and piped supplies stopped.In Chennai, Ravisankar says a long-term solution is needed. Rainfall in southern India this week was 30% below normal levels, according to the India Meteorological Department.“Right now, there’s an emergency so the government is bringing water by trains,” Ravisankar said, referring to supplies that are typically reserved for drinking water instead of hospitals. “But beyond this? It’s all left to nature.”]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70155777/drought-forces-doctors-to-buy-water-for-surgery.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562744981]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semi-Final: Brendon McCullum, Kevin Pietersen Engage In Banter Over New Zealand's Projected Total Against India]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-brendon-mccullum-kevin-pietersen-engage-in-banter-over-new-2067170]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[New Zealand were a mediocre 211/5 off 46.1 overs in the World Cup 2019 semi-final with India when rain halted play on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/fu1v7s88_ross-taylor-tom-latham-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562744295]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Chunky Panday On Comeback In Bollywood After 8 Years In Bangladesh]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/after-8-years-in-bangladesh-chunky-panday-returned-to-bollywood-people-had-forgotten-me-2067168]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chunky Panday said he left to work in the Bangladesh film industry due to lack of lucrative offers in India.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/cp1sn3no_chunky-panday-instagram_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562744137]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Fortnite v9.3 Content Update Brings Air Strike for Summoning Missile Attacks]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/games/news/fortnite-v9-3-content-update-air-strike-battle-royale-creative-save-the-world-2067166]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latest Fornite v9.3 content update brings a new item called Air Strike which can be used to call a missile attack for decimating enemies on a larger scale.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/fortnite_air_strike_1562743763543.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562744059]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India passenger vehicle sales slump in June]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/c8zSS_CNAc4/india-passenger-vehicle-sales-slump-in-june-idINKCN1U50NG]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India's passenger vehicles sales slumped 17.54% in June, an auto industry body said on Wednesday, resulting in an 18.4% fall in sales in the first quarter.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190710&t=2&i=1406401519&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF690E9]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562744047]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Great days over for Eicher, Page, not yet for TCS: Dipen Sheth]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/expert-view/great-days-may-be-over-for-eicher-and-page-but-it-is-still-playing-out-for-tcs-dipen-sheth/articleshow/70155500.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a $7-billion digital slice, 21x valuations, you should buy TCS on dip, buy the little softness in the reporting, says Dipen Sheth, Head, Institutional research, HDFC Securities. Excerpts from interview with ETNOW.Let us talk about IndiGo first. Yes, there are corporate governance issues, long drawn out battle, the impact on the stock regardless of the fact that it is a company that has great valuations, doing well and has had no complaints till now. How would you digest this news?We will be watching this space closely. Any kind of spat at the ownership or sponsor or promoter level is a problem. God knows MindTree is going through some such thing right now. Internal management quality is wonderful. The quality of the business is beyond question. But there is an ownership issue and who is really going to drive this ship is the question. The sena (army) is good but if I am not sure about the senapati (General), then I do not know what this army is going to do.  Somewhere down the line, both realised that they will destroy value if the spat continues. I hate to take sides here or suggest a way out. It is not my mandate of brief but if one of the litigants withdraws respectfully and decides to let the value remain intact and maybe agree to encash the value, it may be solved. I do not know which one it should be and there are various schools of thought around that. Frankly we need to get into the details. But anything that disturbs the mood of two senapatis will rattle the sena. That is the fear we have in MindTree, that is the fear we should have in IndiGo and we should wait for the news bites to die down and for them to put their heads together and work a way out. Aviation is becoming so interesting because we have seen what has happened with Jet. At Air India, they are talking divestment but anyway let us keep that aside for the moment. There is the growth potential.There is SpiceJet, another wonderful management, let us not forget Ajay Singh. Yes so then, it is the only beneficiary in this game?It is not that your loss is my gain, first of all. It played out that way with Jet because in that case, there were horrible operating cost structures and they were overleveraged and there were reckless expansions, coupled with some well founded concerns on corporate governance.   I do not think we have a similar problem in say SpiceJet at all. In fact, I see a money spinner in IndiGo and I am willing to go out on a limb and say Air India’s franchise, its slot, its multi-location advantage across India and the world, makes it a great case for divestment and efficient management which it is not right now.  The sector needs to grow, if there is so much untapped potential….It is not about the growth needs of the sector, the bigger deal is that the sector can grow. This is one of those sectors for India from a five or ten-year perspective where anywhere between 5% and 15% volume growth every year is feasible. Something like a 10% to 12% volume CAGR is easily achievable for a decade. After the strong performance in Q4, TCS has started off on a fairly slow pitch. How have you read into the numbers and experts are saying that there are going to be more headwinds for the stock ahead? You can tick all the negative boxes if you are pessimist on TCS. The US has had a great three-year run on micros. TCS has had an even better run if you look at it that way. It is now a $20-plus billion company. You are looking at hopefully India’s currency not continuously depreciating in the foreseeable future although the jury is out on that. You are looking at digital disruption hitting the sector continuously over the last two years and a lot of people getting it and not getting it and all that kind of thing.  If that is the lens you want to look at TCS through and of course the upcoming talent crunch and shortage for onsite talent in the US, you can keep finding gaps and the fact that TCS continues to be a services play rather than a product play like the glam dogs in the innovation space within IT. However, you got a $20-billion pure services company with an interesting layer of consulting which is highly respected in the US. When we travelled through the US less than a year ago and spoke with stakeholders across the industry value chain -- customers or competitors, consultants, global innovators companies and so on -- there was uniform respect for the management quality and the delivery efficiency and the reliability of TCS.  Within India’s software space, TCS is the Mercedes Benz of delivery. I do not see that changing. Now they have got a $7-billion digital practice as well. Yes legacy has slowed down and in fact it is just about flat year on year and you will crib about the headline growth not being 3% and 2 point something, the margin slipping from the 26% band to somewhere around 24% and all of that, but with a $7-billion digital slice, 21x valuations, you should buy the dip, you should buy the little softness in the reporting.  It is just around the Rs 2100 mark...Yes so who is selling? Nobody. You can crib all you want on TCS but a great company with slightly higher or little higher than industry valuations is not to be sold. There is no sign that the greatness is going away. Once you see greatness going away, you may not want to give a premium valuations. It has played out in Eicher. It has played out in Page. But it is not playing out for TCS because they continue to deliver within a certain range. It will always be a half or a one per cent up or below what you think it should have been, but there is no breakdown of the thesis at all.  Is it playing out for Bajaj Finance?There is a contradictory thing coming through. First of all, the disclaimer that we do not have them under coverage and we have been trying to figure them out and this is a company that ticks all the boxes just like TCS and while we do not have them under coverage, and we do not have a formal recommendation. There is nothing to my mind which suggests that a little bit of caution reported by Mr Bajaj should be taken as a five-year commentary. He will go through ups and downs, the business will go through ups and downs but look at that growth and look at the sustainability of that growth and look at that growth coming without spoiling the quality of the balance sheet.  Well there is a thought that came in from one of our other market participants saying that the risk of default would filter down to small ticket loans also. Yes of course, so they just do not want expectations to run ahead of reality and if you have smaller ticket size loan, remember the risk is granular and mostly manageable there out of process rather than solid person to person underwriting skills, the thing that happens in a Rs 500-crore corporate loan. The kind of risk management skills needed there are completely different from the risk management skills which are needed in a Rs 10,000 mobile loan.  The Rs 10,000 mobile loan can actually be automated and be powered with artificial intelligence and risk analytics in a way that the Rs 500-crore corporate loan cannot be. I am much more bullish on the prospects for Bajaj Finance than on the prospects for many of the corporate banks which are now healing very fast. Financials is really what everyone is betting on in terms of a certain segment within the broader pack, hoping that some of the monetary stimulus will start to kick in, that the cleanup is behind us. Would you agree or would you still be a little cautious?No at one-third or so of the lead index, financial is where you must be focussing very closely but as this market has taught us for the last few years, it is not going to be broad- based move and you will see divergence in performance, you will see divergence in valuations and you will be puzzled to see even more divergence in their commentary and in the way the stock eventually performs. You will continue to be puzzled by the relative outperformance of what is good but you feel it is too costly and that has played out for Bajaj Finance.  It will continue to play out for some of the bigger banks and it is time that Axis and ICICI Bank got back to their old premium valuations. Axis has many more miles to cover on the valuation front although some brokers have recently said that is the big valuation re-rating game ever. There are many levers at Axis and of course at ICICI Bank. Whether it is growth, balance sheet healing, sharpening of core metric as you move forward, Axis after the big blowout on asset quality has got less than 2% of their loan book to BB and below quality. We see even here for the next two years, provisioning or credit costs falling appreciably over the next two-three years. , Now you have an inspirational leader in charge who is being able to attract talent from HDFC Bank and that is inspiring as an observer.What about an IndusInd?IndusInd is a very interesting case. There is no question on management quality there. They have had that accident with IL&FS but they have been running a brilliant operation for more than a decade now. They are reasonably valued. This is a very good opportunity to look at IndusInd all over again because with by adding the Bharat Financial slice to their loan book one, gives them diversification and a ROA higher than their average ROA kind of loan book with relatively lower consumption of capital. Are they buying more risk? I think they are getting more opportunity. There are two ways again to look at this, they are getting far more reach into up-country India. The opportunity for eventual cross-sell may not be there right now, but eventual cross-sell of a whole lot of financial products down that channel is tremendous. They have been punished God knows enough for their accidents with IL&FS and as they transitioned to Ind-AS, some of their bloated fee income reporting might get a little averaged out, but I wouldn’t be worried on that. The big deal here is can they keep a tight grip here on the slight shake up that has happened in asset quality and Bharat Financial can continue to deliver on what is clearly a very high opportunity lending slice, lending vertical in microfinance. I suspect there is going to be serious value creation all over again in IndusInd Bank. What is the view on FMCG space? Do you believe this is an opportunity to enter, is there more pain?It is fashionable to beat FMCG saying that oh! valuations are at 40, 45, 50 and all of that. Rural India is going through a slowdown so FMCG will underperform. God knows it has not underperformed in the last five or 50 years, so long as we remain the broader comment on FMCG so long as we remain a consumption up skilling driven economy any consumer business is set for a good time that said some consumer businesses have more cyclicality or vulnerability. Let us say so a business like Symphony. I am going outside FMCG to illustrate my point. A business like Symphony has more vulnerability to reported weather, a business like Voltas has more vulnerability to consumer sentiment because after all it is discretionary spend. On FMCG the big deal is that you need to look at quality of portfolio. Hindustan Lever stands out as there is just no comparison with Hindustan Lever and Nestle, though we do not have Nestle under coverage. These two companies completely stand out but and niche stories like Marico, the vulnerability on Marico has been that they have not had a single a very large product success or brand success for sometime, but they are a very gifted management and the advantage that they got over the last 6 to 12 months was the gradual falling off of the copra price cycle which they play to advantage and delivered alpha for investors.I do not think we should look at it purely from a copra cycle perspective either. You do have high quality businesses. I must confess like Marico, like Britannia and Lever, you have to take your pick in terms of where you find the valuations comforting. I must confess that ITC at 40-45% discount to the sector is alluring even though it is a sin industry and the stock has gone nowhere. If I can round up my views on the entire consumer space and not just FMCG, I must confess that despite the headline high valuations, I also like Jubilant Foodworks for the sheer management quality and the reinvention of the business model over the last year and a half or so. Much of that is still to deliver, especially in terms of their digital evolution and you have no idea what you can do. They are a food tech company and a consumer company combined into one and you have no idea of the addressable opportunity that they are looking at, the kind of levers they are pulling in terms of internal efficiencies getting revamped and getting driven by digitalisation. The 37-38x kind of valuation multiples are not too scary. The stock has gone nowhere over the last few months and this is a good time to pick it up.What are you making of the higher tax on FPIs? In your notes you have said that it may not be a bad thing?That is again a slightly higher level comment. I have always been personally uncomfortable about the fact that I can invest in my markets at a tax rate which is different from foreigners level playing field. Mutual funds are not taxed for the simple reason that they are pass through instruments. As an investor in a mutual fund, I am liable to pay short term or long term whatever the case might be. Long-term capital gains of 10% may be regressive but it is not significant enough to kill the sentiment for investing. Long-term investment in the stock market should be incentivised. Given the very low penetration that equities have in our household savings pie, may be the thing to do is perhaps to take up the holding period to two years or even three! Why not and say we will tax you at zero rates for that. This is one suggestion I have for the government. The second thing is on the FPI bit. I want simplification and I want FPIs to be treated the same way as let us say Indian corporates would be treated if they were to invest in the stock markets and in fact FPI should be treated at par with mutual funds in so far as that if mutual funds are pass through instruments, the eventual beneficiaries of FPI holdings. If you cannot pass through the tax impact, then you need to tax them as and when they book those profits in the stock market and I am okay with that. I do not think there is much to crib there. Having said that, overall on taxation front, the budget has been a little harsher than it could have been and I am not complaining about the 42 or 43% effective on the higher tax slabs. A lot of the rich folks will crib on that I think it is okay, I do not think it is a big deal. For me the bigger deal is the taxability, getting more people in the tax net. The good work that was started by Aadhaar by digitalising or digitising the IT or Income Tax.Digitising IT infrastructure was a good idea, Aadhaar was a good idea and the DeMon was a good idea in terms of trying to get more people in the tax net, putting up withholding tax on large cash withdrawals is a good idea. But there are a whole lot of people who are still outside the tax net and who are taxable. I wish the government would do something tight and something strong to get them into the tax net maybe then we can let go of the 45% or 43% tax rates.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70155500/great-days-over-for-eicher-page-not-yet-for-tcs-dipen-sheth.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743990]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Singapore's 'Priciest Penthouse': $54 Million, 3 Floors, 5 Bedrooms]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/singapores-priciest-penthouse-54-million-3-floors-5-bedrooms-2067163]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[British billionaire inventor James Dyson has paid a reported $54 million for Singapore's biggest, most expensive penthouse: a three-floor residence with a rooftop terrace, private pool, and jacuzzi.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/gdj6f8d8_james-dyson-singapore-pent-afp-_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743986]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[After Kangana Boycott, Ekta Kapoor Apologises For 'Untoward Incident']]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/after-kangana-ranaut-boycott-ekta-kapoor-apologises-for-untoward-incident-2067162]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ekta Kapoor wrote, "Because it happened at the event of our film, we, as the producers would like to apologize for this untoward incident."]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/mim8u7g_ekta-kapoor-ndtv_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743961]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Population Day 2019 Theme, Significance And Why It Is Celebrated]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/health/world-population-day-2019-theme-significance-and-why-it-is-celebrated-2067150]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[World Population Day 2019 aims at focusing people's attention towards population issues and how it affects overall growth and development plans and programs.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/rtq4erdrvze_world-population-day-2018_625x300.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743913]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Deposits in Jan Dhan accounts cross Rs 1 lakh crore]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/industry/banking/finance/banking/deposits-in-jan-dhan-accounts-cross-rs-1-lakh-crore/articleshow/70155469.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deposits in bank accounts opened under Jan Dhan scheme, launched about five years ago by the Modi-government, have crossed the Rs 1 lakh crore mark.  As per the latest finance ministry data, the total balance in over 36.06 crore Pradhan Mantri Jan Dhan Yojana (PMJDY) accounts was at Rs 1,00,495.94 crore as on July 3.  The deposits in the account of the beneficiaries, which has been steadily rising, was Rs 99,649.84 crore on June 6 and Rs 99,232.71 crore in the week before.  The PMJDY was launched on August 28, 2014, with an aim to provide universal access to banking facilities to the people in the country.  Accounts opened under PMJDY are Basic Savings Bank Deposit (BSBD) accounts with additional feature of RuPay debit card and overdraft.  The finance ministry had recently said in the Rajya Sabha that the number of zero balance accounts under PMJDY declined from 5.10 crore (16.22 per cent of the total accounts) in March 2018 to 5.07 crore (14.37 per cent of the total accounts) in March 2019.  More than 28.44 crore account holders have been issued the Rupay debit cards.  There is no requirement of maintaining minimum balance in BSBD accounts.  Enthused by the success of the scheme, the government enhanced the accident insurance cover to Rs 2 lakh from Rs 1 lakh for new accounts opened after August 28, 2018.  The overdraft limit has also been doubled to Rs 10,000.  The government also shifted the focus on accounts from 'every household' to 'every unbanked adult'.  Over 50 per cent of the Jan Dhan account holders are women.  The objective of PMJDY is to ensure access to various financial services like availability of basic savings bank account, access to need based credit, remittances facility, insurance and pension to weaker sections and low income groups.  The PMJDY also envisages channelling all government benefits to the beneficiary accounts and pushing the Direct Benefit Transfer (DBT) scheme of the central government.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70155469/deposits-in-jan-dhan-accounts-cross-rs-1-lakh-crore.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743406]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[IND vs NZ semi-final: Manchester weather updates]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/manchester-weather-updates-advantage-india-with-semi-final-to-be-completed-on-reserve-day/articleshow/70153705.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As per the rain rules of the International Cricket Council (ICC), if there is no play possible on the reserve match day and no winner is determined, the higher placed team from the league stage will progress to the final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153872,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1330001,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743244]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Australia vs England Semi Final Preview: England Eye Final Berth, Face Daunting Australia]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/australia-vs-england-preview-icc-semi-final-world-cup-2019-england-face-daunting-arch-rivals-austral-2067145]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aus vs Eng Match Preview: Four years of planning will be put on the line for England when they face Australia in a World Cup 2019 semi-final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/6gjli21g_australia-vs-england-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562743122]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Dutee Chand First Indian Woman To Win 100m Gold In World Universiade]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/othersports/dutee-chand-wins-100m-gold-at-world-university-games-says-pull-me-down-will-come-back-stronger-2067037]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dutee Chand won the gold medal in women's 100-metre sprint at the 30th Summer University Games in Italy, becoming the first Indian to do so.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/2mkslvao_dutee-chand-twitter_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562742885]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[MCC Revises Round 2 NEET Counsellling Schedule]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/education/neet-counselling-2019-mcc-round-2-allotment-schedule-update-medicalcounseling-nic-in-mcc-nic-in-2067143]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The NEET counselling including the registration and allotment process will be held at medicalcounseling.nic.in or mcc.nic.in.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562742691]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[BSNL Offers 2GB Daily Data Benefits Through Rs. 186, 187 Prepaid Plans]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/telecom/news/bsnl-rs-186-187-prepaid-recharge-plan-upgrade-2gb-data-per-day-benefits-2067141]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rs. 186 and Rs. 187 BSNL prepaid plans bring 2GB daily data benefits over earlier 1GB data per day for 28 days.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/bsnl_logo_1555681445829.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562742625]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Realme 3i to Sport Helio P60 SoC and 4GB RAM, Geekbench Listing Tips]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/realme-3i-geekbench-listing-helio-p60-4gb-ram-android-pie-2067129]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Realme 3i is likely to come as a cheaper variant of the Realme 3 that was launched earlier this year.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/realme_main_1562742112723.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562742124]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About 4K and HDR Before Buying a TV]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tv/news/what-is-4k-hdr-tv-should-i-buy-upgrade-guide-2066522]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[You may have heard that 4K and HDR offer improved picture quality, but what exactly are they? Read on to find out.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/4k_tv_explainer_main_2_unsplash_1562654009613.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562741276]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ITI Delhi Delhi Rank List Released. Check Here]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/education/iti-delhi-admission-2019-iti-delhi-rank-list-itidelhiadmissions-nic-in-2067119]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ITI rank list for the ITI Delhi admission is available on the official website of the counselling, itidelhiadmissions.nic.in.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/g52tsro_students_625x300_22_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562741024]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Zoom Makes a U-Turn, Releases a Patch for Security Flaw in Its Mac App]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/apps/news/zoom-mac-app-emergency-patch-security-flaw-jonathan-leitschuh-july-12-2067118]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zoom has pushed out an emergency patch to kill the controversial local Web server installed by its Mac app in a surprise U-turn.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/zoom_mac_1562653394681.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562741011]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[IND vs NZ semi-final: Manchester weather updates]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/manchester-weather-updates-advantage-india-with-semi-final-to-be-completed-on-reserve-day/articleshow/70153705.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As per the rain rules of the International Cricket Council (ICC), if there is no play possible on the reserve match day and no winner is determined, the higher placed team from the league stage will progress to the final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153872,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1330001,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562740928]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[New-Look Ram Kapoor Shares Before-After Pics Post Massive Weight Loss]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/new-look-ram-kapoor-shares-before-after-pics-after-massive-weight-loss-2067117]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In his latest post, Ram Kapoor juxtaposed his old pictures with his post-transformation photos.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/4v6agrr_ram-kapoor-instagram_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562740576]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Gender Reveal Party Goes Terribly Wrong As Car Bursts Into Flames]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/offbeat/gender-reveal-party-goes-terribly-wrong-as-car-bursts-into-flames-2067114]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Queensland Police released drone footage of the gender reveal gone wrong to warn others against attempting such stunts. The video shows a man's car bursting into flames on the Gold Coast while he was...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ivrc8bao_australia-gender-reveal_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562740444]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Serena Williams Moved Past US Open Controversy After Therapy And An Apology]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/serena-williams-moved-past-us-open-controversy-after-therapy-and-an-apology-2067104]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the days following her loss to Naomi Osaka in the 2018 U.S. Open final, Serena Williams had trouble falling asleep at her Florida home.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/kgau6du_serena-williams-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562739768]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Karnataka SSLC Supplementary Result Soon. Check Date Update Here.]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/education/karnataka-sslc-supplementary-result-2019-kseeb-kar-nic-in-karresults-nic-in-date-update-2067108]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Karnataka SSLC supplementary results are expected to be released at kseeb.kar.nic.in, or at karresults.nic.in.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/nv6nle5g_result_625x300_25_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562739692]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Two Buildings Collapse In Bengaluru, 4 Killed; Rescue Operations On]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/bangalore-news/bengaluru-two-buildings-collapse-in-pulikeshi-nagar-4-killed-2067105]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the labourers who died in the under-construction building collapse has been identified as Sambu Kumar from Bihar.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/dtd7chfo_building-collapse-bengaluru_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562739538]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[IND vs NZ semi-final: Manchester weather updates]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/manchester-weather-updates-advantage-india-with-semi-final-to-be-completed-on-reserve-day/articleshow/70153705.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As per the rain rules of the International Cricket Council (ICC), if there is no play possible on the reserve match day and no winner is determined, the higher placed team from the league stage will progress to the final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153872,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1330001,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562739389]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Worsening Drought Forcing Chennai Doctors to Buy Water for Surgeries]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/chennai-news/worsening-drought-forcing-chennai-doctors-to-buy-water-for-surgeries-2067102]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with other doctors in Indian cities facing unprecedented water shortages, T.N. Ravisankar in Chennai is praying for rain-and soon.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/2k647gbg_chennai-hospital-bloomberg_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562739320]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Opinion: 4 Things Need To Urgently Fix In India's Education System]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/opinion/4-things-need-to-urgently-fix-in-indias-education-system-2066554]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[We did not really need a policy document; what we need is an action document on strategy and implementation, one that identifies the few most significant issues and then details how these can be...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.ndtvimg.com/i/2018-02/exam-generic-students-generic-pti_650x400_41517903905.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562739093]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Former England Spinner Monty Panesar Feels Rain Break Will Help India In World Cup Semi-Final]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-monty-panesar-feels-rain-break-will-help-india-2067077]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India's World Cup semi-final clash against New Zealand was moved to the reserve day due to rain at Old Trafford on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ki7ok8m_team-india-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562738920]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019, Australia vs England Semi-Final: Peter Handscomb All Set For World Cup Debut]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/australia-vs-england-world-cup-semi-final-peter-handscomb-all-set-for-world-cup-debut-against-englan-2067044]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Peter Handscomb was left out of Australia's initial 15-man squad after the return of Steve Smith and David Warner from year-long ball-tampering bans.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ba0vvig8_peter-handscomb-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562738688]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Salman Gets An 'Urvashi' Dance Lesson From Prabhu Deva Himself]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/salman-khan-gets-an-urvashi-dance-lesson-from-prabhu-deva-himself-how-did-he-do-2067094]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Salman Khan and Sudeep lined up as Prabhu Deva taught them the basic dance moves of Urvashi.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/qe27d218_salman-khan-instagram_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562738528]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[IND vs NZ semi-final: Manchester weather updates]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/manchester-weather-updates-advantage-india-with-semi-final-to-be-completed-on-reserve-day/articleshow/70153705.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As per the rain rules of the International Cricket Council (ICC), if there is no play possible on the reserve match day and no winner is determined, the higher placed team from the league stage will progress to the final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153872,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1330001,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562738150]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[We play to be best in the world: Novak Djokovic on evergreen trio]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/we-play-to-be-best-in-the-world-novak-djokovic-on-evergreen-trio/articleshow/70154058.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some storylines are evergreen. Wimbledon's top-three - Novak Djokovic, Roger Federer and Rafael Nadal. The rapier two-handed backhand, the precision of the serve and the viciously spun forehand is back in a major quarterfinal. Again.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70154078,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1158587,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562737862]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Xi Jinping Tells Officials Not To Be Lazy And "Spend Whole Day Eating"]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/chinese-president-xi-jinping-tells-officials-not-to-be-lazy-and-spend-whole-day-eating-2067081]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese officials must not use the fight against corruption as an excuse to sit around and do nothing, idling their time away and "spending the whole day eating", President Xi Jinping told a meeting...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/p798tg58_xi-jinping-reuters_625x300_07_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562737554]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Congress's DK Shivakumar's Biggest Challenge As Karnataka Crisis Deepens]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/congresss-dk-shivakumars-biggest-challenge-as-karnataka-crisis-deepens-2067080]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A senior Mumbai police officer, stopping Mr Shivakumar from entering the hotel, said: "Sir, (the rebel lawmakers) have said they are frightened of you, we can't allow you to enter unless they want us...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/j8dis8m8_dk-shivakumar_625x300_10_July_19.jpeg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562737494]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Serena Williams seeks to equal Margaret Court's Grand Slam record]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/serena-williams-seeks-to-equal-margaret-courts-grand-slam-record/articleshow/70153955.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The warrior in Serena Williams is alive and kicking. Centre Court got a live demonstration as did her battling opponent of the day - American Alison Riske.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153964,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1187152,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562737428]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Dawood Ibrahim's Activities From 'Safe Haven' Pose A Danger: India to UN]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/dawoods-illegitimate-activities-from-safe-haven-pose-real-danger-india-to-united-nations-security-co-2067076]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a veiled attack on Pakistan, India has told the United Nations Security Council (UNSC) that Dawood Ibrahim's illegitimate activities from a "safe haven" that refuses to acknowledge even his...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-03/5rdu2t2_syed-akbaruddin-twitter_625x300_29_March_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562736888]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Former England Batsmen Slam "Awful" Wicket For India vs New Zealand World Cup Semi-Final]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-former-england-batsmen-slam-awful-wicket-at-old-trafford-2067061]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[New Zealand found run-scoring tough on what many observers agreed was a slow and two-paced surface.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/3qcq8hno_manchester-rain-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562735673]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Mozilla Blocks UAE Bid to Become an Internet Security Guardian]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/internet/news/mozilla-blocks-uae-bid-to-become-an-internet-security-guardian-after-hacking-reports-2067060]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firefox browser maker Mozilla is blocking the United Arab Emirates' government from serving as one of its Internet security gatekeepers.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/mozilla_reuters_full_1562735518531.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562735633]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Redmi Note 7 Series Shipments Cross 15 Million Units Worldwide in 6 Months]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/redmi-note-7-pro-15-million-worldwide-shipments-donovan-sung-2067059]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the end of May this year, Xiaomi confirmed that the Redmi Note 7 series had reached the 10 million mark .]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/redmi_note_7_pro_neptune_blue_1560887630085.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562735579]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Man With Fake ID Arrested For Trying To Defraud Government Ministries]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/man-with-fake-id-arrested-in-delhi-for-trying-to-defraud-government-ministries-2067056]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A 21-year-old man was arrested on Tuesday for creating a fake identity card of a Pay and Accounts Officer (PAO officer )of the central government to siphon off money from the bank accounts of various...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/acv94b7g_delhi-police-generic_625x300_24_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562734953]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019: Old Trafford turns into 'no-fly zone']]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/world-cup-2019-old-trafford-turns-into-no-fly-zone/articleshow/70153326.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Old Trafford stadium was made a "No Fly Zone" for India's semifinal clash against New Zealand, an action prompted by a private plane displaying anti-India banners during the team's league encounter against Sri Lanka in Headingley.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153333,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1169856,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562734271]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Former England batsmen slam WC semi-final pitch]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/former-england-batsmen-slam-awful-world-cup-semi-final-pitch/articleshow/70152911.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Former England batsmen Graeme Fowler and Mark Butcher both took to Twitter to condemn the "awful" pitch used for the World Cup semi-final between India and New Zealand at Old Trafford on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153284,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1234901,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562734212]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup: What happens if semis or final is washed out?]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/icc-world-cup-what-happens-if-semis-or-final-is-washed-out/articleshow/70139466.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fickle English weather has made an impact on matches more than once during the 2019 ICC World Cup. Four of the 45 league matches were washed out, the most in a single edition of the ODI World Cup.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70139467,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1200941,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562734012]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019, Australia vs England Semi-Final: Peter Handscomb All Set For World Cup Debut]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/australia-vs-england-world-cup-semi-final-peter-handscomb-all-set-for-world-cup-debut-against-englan-2067044]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Peter Handscomb was left out of Australia's initial 15-man squad after the return of Steve Smith and David Warner from year-long ball-tampering bans.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ba0vvig8_peter-handscomb-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562733858]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rain takes India-New Zealand World Cup semifinal into reserve day]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/world-cup-2019-rain-takes-india-new-zealand-world-cup-semifinal-into-reserve-day/articleshow/70151780.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The World Cup semifinal between India and New Zealand will head into a second day after rain prevented the match finishing as scheduled at Old Trafford on Tuesday. New Zealand had struggled to 211/5 off 46.1 overs when persistent rain worsened sufficiently for the umpires to halt play with 23 balls left in the innings.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70151898,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1270192,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562733771]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Kane Williamson plays lone ranger, again]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-2019-kane-williamson-plays-lone-ranger-again/articleshow/70153156.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Batting first against India in the World Cup semifinal, Kane Williamson again came to his team's rescue with a classy 67, his fourth 50-plus score in the tournament which includes two centuries. Williamson steadied the ship and gave New Zealand something to play with. His 67 took his World Cup tally to 548 in eight innings at an astounding average of 91.33.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70153161,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1180792,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562733573]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump's Blocking of Twitter Critics Unconstitutional: US Appeals Court]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/social-networking/news/trumps-blocking-of-twitter-critics-unconstitutional-us-appeals-court-2067046]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a 3-0 decision, the 2nd US Circuit Court of Appeals in Manhattan said the First Amendment forbids Trump from using Twitter's "blocking" function to limit access to his account, which has 61.8...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/donald_trump_reuters_1558672254158.JPG]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562733540]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[These Premium Phones Will Receive Discounts on Prime Day 2019 Sale in India]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/amazon-prime-day-2019-sale-india-deals-on-premium-smartphones-2066125]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day 2019 sale kicks off next week and the online marketplace has revealed a list of popular premium smartphones that will receive discounts during the sale.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/Onelus_7_Pro_front_ndtv_1557756254148.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562732518]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Kevin Pietersen's Hilarious 'Dola Re Dola' Meme Is A Viral Hit]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/offbeat/kevin-pietersens-hilarious-dola-re-dola-meme-is-a-viral-hit-2067040]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Kevin Pietersen shared the hilarious pic of himself Photoshopped into a still from the song 'Dola Re Dola' from Devdas.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/46qss15s_kevin-pietersen_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562732427]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Redmi K20, Redmi K20 Pro Pre-Bookings Start July 12 in India]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/redmi-k20-pro-alpha-sale-details-july-12-price-specifications-expected-rs-855-booking-amount-2066197]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[This Redmi K20 alpha sale will enable users to reserve a unit for themselves before the actual sale beckons after July 17, by paying a nominal amount.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/redmi_k20_series_one_million_1561958746301.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562732080]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019, India vs New Zealand, Manchester Weather Forecast: Intermittent Rain Expected On Reserve Day]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-manchester-weather-forecast-2067017]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India will be through to the World Cup 2019 final if the match is called off on the reserve day because of their higher position on the points table.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ju1dfl58_manchester-rain-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562731839]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Realme 3i Set to Debut in India Alongside Realme X]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/realme-3i-india-launch-date-july-15-specifications-features-2066515]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realme 3i is expected to be a cheaper variant of the Realme 3 that was back in March with a starting price of Rs. 8,999.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/realme_3_1562653066372.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562731823]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Dutee Chand Wins 100m Gold At World University Games, Says "Pull Me Down, Will Come Back Stronger"]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/othersports/dutee-chand-wins-100m-gold-at-world-university-games-says-pull-me-down-will-come-back-stronger-2067037]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dutee Chand won the gold medal in women's 100-metre sprint at the 30th Summer University Games in Italy, becoming the first Indian to do so.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/2mkslvao_dutee-chand-twitter_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562731777]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[It's quite unfair to criticise Dhoni, says Kapil Dev]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/world-cup-2019-its-quite-unfair-to-criticise-dhoni-says-kapil-dev/articleshow/70152790.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[MS Dhoni has come up with decent scores in the World Cup, but what the scorecards don't reflect is his inability to rotate the strike and strike big. Some have attributed it to the lack of intent and some have pointed out the his waning capabilities as a finisher, something that had once made him a top short format player in the world.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70152799,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1260970,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562731577]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Downgrade rate accelerates on liquidity pressure, weak margins]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/rate-of-downgrades-accelerates-on-liquidity-pressure-weak-margins/articleshow/70152869.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India’s credit market is going through challenging times with the credit quality, as measured by CARE Ratings’ ‘modified credit ratio’ (MCR), for the June quarter declining to a six-year low of 0.8 times.The share of downgrades by Care in total rating actions more than doubled to 26 per cent in June 2019 quarter compared to 12 per cent in June 2018 quarter, while share of upgrades declined from 13 per cent to 7 per cent during this period. Sectors like auto, chemicals, NBFCs, cement, real estate and food processing, among others, have seen a deterioration in credit quality in April-June quarter, according to Care.Only four sectors -- Information technology, electricity transmission & distribution, healthcare and hospitality -- have seen improved credit ratio in June 2019 quarter when compared to the same period a year ago. Improvement in the financial position and a favourable liquidity position prompted rating upgrades in the IT sector.
  
  70152832




“There has been deterioration in the credit quality of entities rated by CARE Ratings in the first quarter of the ongoing financial year which attests to the prevailing slowdown in the domestic economy,” said Arun Kumar, executive director, Care Ratings. “The credit rating downgrades of entities in June 2019 quarter has been largely on account of liquidity pressure leading to delays in debt servicing, high debt levels, weakening profit margins, decline in scale of operations, deterioration in capital structure and debt coverage indicators.”While the moderation in credit quality, which is indicative of the higher number of credit rating downgrades, has been across categories and sectors, it has been more pronounced in the case of small enterprises with total revenues of less than Rs 100 crore.
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70152869/downgrade-rate-accelerates-on-liquidity-pressure-weak-margins.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562731369]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Serena Williams Battles Through At Wimbledon, Simona Halep Storms Back To Reach Semi-Finals]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/serena-williams-battles-through-at-wimbledon-halep-storms-back-to-reach-semi-finals-2067016]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Serena Williams came under enormous pressure from Alison Riske before prevailing in an engrossing contest, 6-4, 4-6, 6-3 in just over two hours.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/6e1qenmg_serena-williams-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562730562]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Andy Murray Rules Out US Open Singles Return]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/andy-murray-rules-out-us-open-singles-return-2067025]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Andy Murray had hinted that his successful hip surgery could pave the way for a dramatic appearance at the season's concluding Grand Slam.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/rm13mhgg_andy-murray-afp_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562730531]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[England face acid test in semi-final clash with Australia]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/australia-vs-england-world-cup-england-face-acid-test-in-semi-final-clash-with-australia/articleshow/70152530.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Four years of planning will be put on the line for England when they face holders Australia in a blockbuster Cricket World Cup semi-final at Edgbaston on Thursday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70152549,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1178848,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562729643]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019, India vs New Zealand: Here's What Happens If It Rains On Reserve Day As Well]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-what-happens-if-semi-final-gets-rained-out-2066175]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[If it continues to rain on the Reserve Day and the India vs New Zealand semi-final is not completed, then India will qualify for the final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ckcn3808_india-_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562729277]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma better than me and my brothers: Mushtaq Mohammad]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/world-cup-2019-rohit-sharma-better-than-me-and-my-brothers-says-mushtaq-mohammad/articleshow/70152306.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma has smashed a record five centuries in a single World Cup to lead the tournament batting charts with 647 runs from eight innings. Rohit is not only breaking records but also providing the platform at the top which is helping Virat Kohli and Co. score big when batting first.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70152314,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1191371,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562728977]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Wimbledon: Federer wary of fresher, stronger Nishikori]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/wimbledon-roger-federer-wary-of-fresher-stronger-kei-nishikori/articleshow/70152400.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Roger Federer believes his Wimbledon quarter-final opponent Kei Nishikori is ready to challenge for Grand Slams after the Japanese number one seems to have found a way to reach the latter stages without getting tangled up in marathon matches.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70152395,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1139349,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562728660]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand World Cup 2019 Semi-final: Rohit Sharma One Of The Greatest ODI Batsmen, Says India Coach Ravi Shastri]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-rohit-sharma-one-of-the-greatest-odi-batsmen-says-india-coach-ravi-s-2066659]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semifinal Match: Rohit Sharma is in tremendous touch in World Cup 2019, having so far scored 647 runs from eight innings.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/m35sqm9g_rohit-sharma-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562728156]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Don't patronise me, says Johanna Konta after Wimbledon loss]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/dont-patronise-me-says-johanna-konta-after-wimbledon-loss/articleshow/70152206.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Johanna Konta did not take kindly to her 34 unforced errors being raised as a topic of discussion after her disappointing 7-6 (7/5), 6-1 defeat to Barbora Strycova in the Wimbledon quarter-finals on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70152267,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1159704,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562728071]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Wimbledon: Svitolina first Ukrainian woman to reach major semis]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/wimbledon-elina-svitolina-becomes-first-ukrainian-woman-to-reach-major-semis/articleshow/70152255.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[If it had not been for a bout of childhood jealously, Elina Svitolina might never have pulled off the nerve-shredding win over Karolina Muchova at Wimbledon on Tuesday that saw her become the first Ukrainian woman to reach the singles semi-finals at a major.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70152281,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1138794,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562728051]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Karnataka Political Crisis: Ghulam Nabi Azad Questions Governors Conduct]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/karnataka-political-crisis-ghulam-nabi-azad-questions-governors-conduct-2067015]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the backdrop of recent political upheaval in Karnataka, senior Congress leader Ghulam Nabi Azad has alleged that the Centre is using Governors to topple opposition governments in states, and raised...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2018-11/tdjufmfo_ghulam-nabi-azad_625x300_22_November_18.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562727173]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[US Spa Turned Down Blind Man, Said "His Kind" Can't Follow Instructions]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-spa-turned-down-blind-man-said-his-kind-cant-follow-instructions-2067014]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A spa in Los Angeles has agreed to change its policies and pay damages to a blind man denied access to the facility on grounds "his kind" would not be able to follow instructions.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/uses2ac8_spa-palace-los-angeles_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562727043]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Bengaluru Under-Construction Building Collapses, 1 Killed]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/bangalore-news/bengaluru-under-construction-building-collapses-1-killed-2067013]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[An under-construction building collapsed in Bengaluru, killing one person and injuring many others. The building was being constructed in the Pulikeshi Nagar area of Bengaluru.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/lu67s1rg_bengaluru-building-collapse-ani_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562726668]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Goa School Librarian Arrested For Thrashing Student, Fracturing Arm]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/cities/goa-school-librarian-arrested-for-thrashing-class-8-student-fracturing-arm-2067011]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A school librarian was arrested on Tuesday for allegedly beating a Class 8 student for wearing shoes to the school library, the police said.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.ndtvimg.com/i/2016-05/arrest-generic_650x400_71463458726.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562726117]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Decoding the budget 2019: Strict rules soon for PSBs buying NBFC assets]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/industry/banking/finance/banking/decoding-the-budget-2019-strict-rules-soon-for-psbs-buying-nbfc-assets/articleshow/70151614.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI: The government may allow state-run lenders to buy only AA and higher rated retail pooled assets of non-banking financial companies (NBFCs) under the scheme announced in the budget on July 5.A senior government official told ET that guidelines for the scheme will be issued within the next 10 days. “We will not be comfortable with state-run lenders taking exposure to builder loans of such NBFCs,” said the official, who did not wish to be identified. He said the liquidity window opened by the Reserve Bank of India is providing additional comfort required by the sector.In her maiden budget speech finance minister Nirmala Sitharaman had announced that for purchase of high-rated pooled assets of financially sound NBFCs, amounting to a total of Rs 1 lakh crore during the current financial year, the government will provide onetime six months’ partial credit guarantee to public sector banks for first loss of up to 10%.70151960

On the budget day, RBI had also announced a scheme allowing banks to borrow from it by pledging their excess government bond holdings to fund the purchase of NBFC assets, which can release up to Rs  1.34 lakh crore.“The scheme is to boost confidence in the industry and help it tide over liquidity issues,” the official said, adding that during pre-budget consultations the understanding was that NBFCs may require such support for a maximum of two quarters.“There is no pressing need for public sector banks to take undue risk,” he said.Two departments of the finance ministry, that of economic affairs and financial services, will work out the guidelines, ensuring that banks do not have exposure to riskier unsecured loans.According to a recent report released by rating agency ICRA, banks have emerged as a large buyer of pooled assets from NBFCs given the liquidity issues faced by the sector during 2018-19. “Proposal to provide one time six months partial credit guarantee to PSBs for first loss of up to 10% will reduce any credit risk in such assets,” it said, even as it noted that with the guarantee being available for only six months, the preference could be for relatively shorterterm retail assets.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70151614/decoding-the-budget-2019-strict-rules-soon-for-psbs-buying-nbfc-assets.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562726083]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Redmi Note 7 Pro to Go on Sale in India at 12pm Today via Flipkart, Mi.com]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/redmi-note-7-pro-sale-today-july-10-flipkart-mi-com-price-in-india-specifications-offers-2066986]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Redmi Note 7 Pro sale offers from Xiaomi include the Jio cashback offer, which bestows double data benefit on all the prepaid recharges worth Rs. 198 and above.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/redmi_note_7_pro_nebula_red_1562710916465.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562724001]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Interpol Issues Global Alert To Trace German Woman Missing From Kerala]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/kerala-news/interpol-issues-global-alert-to-trace-german-woman-missing-from-kerala-2067003]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As mystery swirls around a German national's disappearance, Interpol has issued a yellow notice, a global alert, following a request by Kerala police to trace the woman missing since March 10 when...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2018-10/2j46hlug_police-generic_625x300_27_October_18.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562723438]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Ex-US Vice President Biden, Wife Made $15 Million After Leaving Office]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/ex-us-vice-president-biden-wife-made-over-15-million-after-leaving-office-2067002]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Former US Vice President Joe Biden and his wife, Jill, earned more than $15 million in the two years after Biden left government in early 2017, according to tax records released by his campaign on...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/amkd874g_joe-biden-reuters_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562723094]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Wife, Son, Accomplice Arrested In Central Government Staff's Murder]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/delhi-news/wife-son-accomplice-arrested-in-central-government-staffs-murder-2066996]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A 36-year-old woman and her accomplice were arrested for allegedly killing her husband, an auditor employed with the central government, in southeast Delhi's Jaitpur, the police said on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.ndtvimg.com/i/2017-05/arrest-generic_650x400_41495967190.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562720600]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[U.S., China to relaunch talks with little changed since deal fell apart]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/TrYCs_5bMqM/u-s-china-to-relaunch-talks-with-little-changed-since-deal-fell-apart-idINKCN1U40FE]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The United States and China are set to relaunch trade talks this week after a two-month hiatus, but a year after their trade war began there is little sign their differences have narrowed.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406177711&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF68194]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562718867]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[A First: US Puts Hezbollah Lawmakers On Sanctions Blacklist]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/a-first-us-puts-hezbollah-lawmakers-amin-sherri-muhammad-hasan-raad-on-sanctions-blacklist-2066995]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The US Treasury placed two Hezbollah members of Lebanon's parliament on its sanctions blacklist on Tuesday -- the first time Washington has taken aim at the Iran-allied group's elected politicians.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/amv1250g_mike-pompeo_625x300_26_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562718011]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rebel Karnataka Lawmakers Seek Protection As Kumaraswamy in Mumbai Today]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/rebel-karnataka-lawmakers-seek-police-protection-as-chief-minister-hd-kumaraswamy-in-mumbai-today-2066992]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rebel Karnataka lawmakers who are camping in Mumbai since Saturday have approached the Mumbai Police, seeking protection from Chief Minister HD Kumaraswamy and senior Congress leader and minister...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/75mokm7o_karnataka-legislators-who-quit-pti_625x300_06_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562716229]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump blasts 'foolish' UK PM May and her 'wacky' envoy over leaked memos]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/LyqEuhnKxwg/trump-blasts-foolish-uk-pm-may-and-her-wacky-envoy-over-leaked-memos-idINKCN1U41BO]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump lashed out at "foolish" British Prime Minister Theresa May and her "wacky" Washington ambassador on Tuesday, stepping up a tirade against a close ally whose envoy had branded his administration inept.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406137197&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680UC]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562705038]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[UP Is Running But Electricity In Hospitals Is Out: Priyanka Gandhi Vadra]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/congress-ggeneral-secretary-priyanka-gandhi-vadra-slams-uttar-pradesh-government-state-running-but-e-2066971]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Congress general secretary Priyanka Gandhi Vadra on Tuesday hit out at the BJP government in Uttar Pradesh over reports of patients being treated in some hospitals under mobile phone flashlights or...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-03/g1n68rus_priyanka-gandhi-vadra-gujarat-twitter_650x400_12_March_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562700113]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Man Slits Teen's Throat After Boy's Rap Song Made Him Feel "Unsafe": Cops]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/arizona-man-slits-teens-throat-after-boys-rap-music-made-him-feel-unsafe-cops-2066970]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Michael Adams, 27, told investigators he heard Al-Amin listening to rap in his car before entering the store - a genre that makes him feel "unsafe" - according to a probable-cause statement reviewed...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/hmbpkma8_michael-adamskillsteen650_625x300_10_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562698725]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Europeans call for urgent meeting of Iran nuclear deal parties]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/4kedQ0poqgY/europeans-call-for-urgent-meeting-of-iran-nuclear-deal-parties-idINKCN1U41IV]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[European powers accused Iran on Tuesday of "pursuing activities inconsistent with its commitments" under a 2015 nuclear deal and called for an urgent meeting of the parties to the agreement to discuss Tehran's compliance.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406168324&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF6816W]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562698426]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Section Of Congress Leaders Want Milind Deora To Be Mumbai Chief: Report]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/section-of-congress-leaders-want-milind-deora-to-be-mumbai-chief-report-2066968]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rumblings in the Mumbai Congress just got louder with a group of leaders on Tuesday requesting AICC general secretary Mallikarjun Kharge not to accept the resignation of Milind Deora as the city...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/jboq289k_milind-deora_625x300_19_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562697954]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Big sports events today]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/more-sports/others/big-sports-events-today/articleshow/70149568.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here are the big sports events lined up for Wednesday (July 10) that comprise the first semi-final of the ICC World Cup 2019 between India and New Zealand which has been deferred to reserve day due to rain.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70149589,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-11009921,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562697900]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019: India vs New Zealand: Semi-Final Goes Into Reserve Day As Rain Affects Big Clash]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-goes-into-reserve-day-as-rain-affects-big-clash-2066955]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand: The semi-final match will resume on Wednesday, as rain suspended the play on Tuesday in Manchester.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/o0eo5qo8_old-trafford-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562697476]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[US Teen Charged With Stealing Jewels, Rolexes, Then Linked To A Lemur]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/us-teen-charged-with-stealing-jewels-rolexes-then-linked-to-a-lemur-2066966]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As they do every other day, employees at the Santa Ana Zoo showed up early on July 28, 2018, to get ready for the public to arrive. This time, however, something was amiss. Lemurs and capuchin monkeys...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/gnoo0pu_aquinas-quinn-kasbar_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562696936]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Drunk Delhi Cop Allegedly Misbehaves With Woman After Hitting Her Car]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/delhi-news/drunk-delhi-cop-allegedly-misbehaves-with-woman-after-hitting-her-car-2066965]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Delhi Commission for Women (DCW) has issued a notice to the city police seeking details about an incident in which a policeman allegedly misbehaved and threatened a woman after hitting her car...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-05/fkcrjpmg_delhi-police-generic_625x300_27_May_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562696900]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[To Help Cops Respond Better To Attacks, These US Students Shoot At Them]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/to-help-cops-respond-better-to-attacks-these-us-students-shoot-at-them-2066962]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a Friday afternoon in April, Texas State University freshman Kendyl Cutshall stopped by a research facility near campus to shoot a police officer for class credit. Inside a simulated classroom...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ja0qsro_to-help-police-respond-better-to-active-shooters-these-students-shoot-at-them-facebook_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562696304]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Cricket: India dominate NZ before rain forces reserve day in Manchester]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/EY__b_tMO_Y/cricket-india-dominate-nz-before-rain-forces-reserve-day-in-manchester-idINKCN1U40WK]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India's disciplined bowling attack dominated New Zealand before intermittent rain washed out the rest of Tuesday's play in the first Cricket World Cup semi-final which will continue on Wednesday.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406202312&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF681EN]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562696240]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi-Final Highlights, World Cup 2019: India-New Zealand Semis Suspended, Match To Resume Tomorrow At 3 pm IST]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-live-cricket-score-match-updates-2066576]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi-final Highlights, 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup: New Zealand reached 211/5 off 46.1 overs before rain stopped play in Manchester.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/lsmjmigg_manchester-weather_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562696149]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sunil Chhetri Named AIFF Player Of Year For Sixth Time]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/football/sunil-chhetri-named-aiff-player-of-year-for-sixth-time-2066961]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sunil Chhetri, who has been in peak form in the last couple of years, has earlier won the honour in 2007, 2011, 2013, 2014 and 2017.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/0qcf85q_sunil-chhetri-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562696042]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA["Not My Fault I Am Gay": Teen Kills Self Over Alleged Discrimination]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/chennai-news/teen-in-chennai-who-killed-self-over-alleged-discrimination-said-not-my-fault-i-am-gay-in-facebook-p-2066958]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A 19-year-old from Mumbai allegedly killed himself by jumping into the sea in Chennai as he was upset over alleged discrimination he faced for being a gay, police said on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2018-11/rqmfkrb_dead-man-body-generic_625x300_29_November_18.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562695922]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Madhya Pradesh Planning Law In Favour Of Locals For Private Sector Jobs]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/madhya-pradesh-planning-law-in-favour-of-locals-for-private-sector-jobs-says-kamal-nath-2066957]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Madhya Pradesh government is planning to bring a law that will ensure that the people of the state will get preference in 70 per cent of the jobs in the private sector, Chief Minister Kamal Nath...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/a1fq5q8c_kamal-nath_625x300_28_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562695630]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019, India vs New Zealand: Here's What Happens If It Rains On Reserve Day As Well]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-what-happens-if-semi-final-gets-rained-out-2066175]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[If it continues to rain on the Reserve Day and the India vs New Zealand semi-final is not completed, then India will qualify for the final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ckcn3808_india-_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562694618]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[John Cena's Special Message For Shilpa's Son Viaan: 'You're Shining Now']]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/wwe-legend-john-cenas-special-message-for-shilpa-shettys-son-viaan-you-are-shining-now-2066954]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA["I saw your video and your muscles... You are enormous," said John Cena in his video]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/i4qfn62_john-cena-viaan_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562694314]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Hyderabad Boy Tries To Hang Self After Classmates Demand Money, Tease Him]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/hyderabad-news/hyderabad-boy-tries-to-hang-self-after-classmates-demand-money-tease-him-2066953]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A tenth standard student attempted suicide at his house in Hyderabad after three of his classmates allegedly harassed and demanded money from him, police said Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/llk3j068_hyderabad-police-650_625x300_14_August_18.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562694274]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Never Left Mumbai, Says Rebel Karnataka Lawmaker, Now In Different Hotel]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/never-left-mumbai-says-rebel-karnataka-lawmaker-now-in-different-hotel-2066952]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A dozen legislators from Karnataka, who flew to Mumbai three days ago after resigning from the state assembly are still camping here, a legislator said, a day after reports said they were being moved...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/1qjongqo_karnataka-mla-congress-protest-mumbai-pti-_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562693879]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rebel AAP Lawmaker Files Plea In Assembly Challenging Disqualification]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/delhi-news/rebel-aap-lawmaker-sandeep-kumar-says-videos-given-by-aaps-saurabh-bhardwaj-in-assembly-not-authenti-2066951]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rebel AAP MLA Sandeep Kumar on Tuesday said he has filed a petition in the Delhi Assembly contending that the videos presented in the House by party spokesperson Saurabh Bhardwaj while seeking his...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.ndtvimg.com/i/2017-08/delhi-assembly-pti_650x400_61502294219.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562693839]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ICC World Cup: India-New Zealand semifinal pushed to reserve day]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/icc-world-cup-india-new-zealand-semifinal-pushed-to-reserve-day/articleshow/70149144.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Manchester weather pushed the first semifinal of the World Cup to the reserve day after Indian bowlers excelled to restrict New Zealand to a sub-par 211/5 in 46.1 overs. The game will resume on Wednesday from where it stopped. If the match doesn't happen on Wednesday, then India will progress to the final by virtue of finishing top in league stage.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70149187,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-195212,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562693736]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump Remarks On Theresa May "Disrespectful, Wrong": UK Foreign Secretary]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/world-news/uk-foreign-secretary-jeremy-hunt-says-donald-trump-remarks-on-theresa-may-disrespectful-wrong-2066950]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[British Foreign Secretary Jeremy Hunt on Tuesday said US President Donald Trump was "disrespectful and wrong" in making disparaging remarks about outgoing Prime Minister Theresa May and her ambassador...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/45di54ts_jeremy-hunt-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562692944]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Thane Man Beats Puppy To Death, Warns Against Entry Of Animals In Complex]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/cities/thane-man-beats-puppy-to-death-warns-against-entry-of-animals-in-complex-say-police-2066948]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A man has been booked in Maharashtra's Thane district for allegedly beating to death a puppy, police said Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/144povgk_police-istock_625x300_15_August_18.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562692752]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump's blocking of Twitter critics unconstitutional: U.S. appeals court]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/U8aLCXDvTf0/trumps-blocking-of-twitter-critics-unconstitutional-u-s-appeals-court-idINKCN1U41NS]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump violated the Constitution by blocking people whose views he disliked from his Twitter account, a federal appeals court ruled on Tuesday.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406156353&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF68124]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562692339]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[TRS Leader Kidnapped By Suspected Maoists In Telangana: Police]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/telangana-news/trs-leader-n-srinivas-rao-kidnapped-by-suspected-maoists-in-telangana-police-2066947]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A TRS leader has been "taken away" by suspected Maoists from his house in Bhadradri-Kothagudem district to the neighbouring Chhattisgarh, police said on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/police-generic-istock_625x300_1529674184579.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562692295]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Centre Won't Initiate Talks With Separatists Anytime Soon, Say Officials]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/centre-wont-initiate-talks-with-separatists-anytime-soon-say-officials-2066946]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The government would not be initiating talks with the Hurriyat anytime soon as the Home Ministry feels talks with separatists would not yield any results, a senior official has told NDTV. "What can...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.ndtvimg.com/i/2015-09/home-ministry-650_650x400_41441986947.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562692108]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump blasts 'foolish' UK PM May and her 'wacky' envoy over leaked memos]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/LyqEuhnKxwg/trump-blasts-foolish-uk-pm-may-and-her-wacky-envoy-over-leaked-memos-idINKCN1U41BO]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump lashed out at "foolish" British Prime Minister Theresa May and her "wacky" Washington ambassador on Tuesday, stepping up a tirade against a close ally whose envoy had branded his administration inept.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406137197&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680UC]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562692100]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[10 Arrested In Madhya Pradesh For Insurance Fraud Worth Crores]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/cities/madhya-pradesh-dhar-10-arrested-for-insurance-fraud-worth-crores-2066943]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ten members of a gang, including a lawyer and a doctor, have been arrested in Madhya Pradesh's Dhar district for allegedly defrauding insurance companies of crores of rupees by forging fake documents...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/2iq8o5c_dhargangndtv650_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562690963]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Couple In Bhopal Arrested Over Alleged Maoist Links]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/india-news/couple-in-bhopal-arrested-over-alleged-maoist-links-2066942]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A couple, suspected to have Maoist links, was arrested on Monday by Uttar Pradesh Police's Anti-Terror Squad (ATS) from a rented house in Bhopal.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/8h7f0vl_bhopal-couple-arrested-over-alleged-maoist-links-_625x300_09_July_19.jpeg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562690938]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[WHO keeps key lung cancer drugs off its essential medicines list]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/GoNt-AJsCco/who-keeps-key-lung-cancer-drugs-off-its-essential-medicines-list-idINKCN1U40YB]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The world's master list of recommended medicines got an update on Tuesday when the World Health Organization (WHO) published a biennial revision, adding 28 drugs including an abortion pill but leaving out several breakthrough treatments for lung cancer.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406132941&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680MN]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562690770]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019: Yograj Singh Takes Jibe At MS Dhoni, Urges Ambati Rayudu To Return]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/yograj-singh-takes-jibe-at-ms-dhoni-urges-ambati-rayudu-to-return-2066941]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yograj Singh has urged Ambati Rayudu to come out of retirement and score plenty of runs in the domestic circuit.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/7ub7p18g_ms-dhoni-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562690688]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[TCS seeks steady growth as key markets face slowdown]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/IQK297r7jUc/tcs-seeks-steady-growth-as-key-markets-face-slowdown-idINKCN1U419F]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India's biggest software services company Tata Consultancy Services Ltd said on Tuesday it was looking to sustain double-digit revenue growth this fiscal year, even as it flagged stress in global capital markets, especially in European banks.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406182227&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680SU]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562689512]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump again says Indian tariffs on U.S. goods unacceptable]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/cYWreWA6GK4/trump-again-says-indian-tariffs-on-u-s-goods-unacceptable-idINKCN1U41GA]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[U.S. President Donald Trump repeated his complaints on Tuesday that India's tariffs on U.S. products were unacceptable but he did not indicate whether he would take any further action in the trade row between the two nations.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406129935&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680WU]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562689371]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trending: Why Kapil Dev Is The Perfect Fit For Ranveer Singh Biopic]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/entertainment/trending-why-kapil-dev-is-the-perfect-fit-for-ranveer-singh-biopic-2066938]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA["Post effects of spending time with Ranveer. He actually brings/adds colours to your life," wrote one user on Twitter]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/h2nvv3k_kapildevtwitter_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562689345]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[IndiGo co-founder turns to SEBI over alleged corporate governance violation]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/eMmVJ9O62hQ/indigo-co-founder-turns-to-sebi-over-alleged-corporate-governance-violation-idINKCN1U41YI]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the co-founders of India's largest airline IndiGo has alleged violation of corporate governance rules at parent company Interglobe Aviation Ltd and asked the securities regulator to intervene.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406180098&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF6819M]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562688990]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Man Chasing Phone Thief In Mumbai Station Falls On Tracks, Dies]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.ndtv.com/mumbai-news/man-chasing-phone-thief-in-mumbai-station-falls-on-tracks-dies-2066936]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A 53-year-old man travelling by a local train chasing a mobile phone thief died after he fell on tracks at Charni Road station in Mumbai, police said on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ll5ohea_mumbai-local-650_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562688783]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[U.S., China to relaunch talks with little changed since deal fell apart]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/TrYCs_5bMqM/u-s-china-to-relaunch-talks-with-little-changed-since-deal-fell-apart-idINKCN1U40FE]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The United States and China are set to relaunch trade talks this week after a two-month hiatus, but a year after their trade war began there is little sign their differences have narrowed.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406177711&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF68194]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562688435]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sunil Chhetri named AIFF Player of Year for sixth time]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/football/top-stories/sunil-chhetri-named-aiff-player-of-year-for-sixth-time/articleshow/70147982.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Talismanic Indian captain Sunil Chhetri was Tuesday named as the AIFF Men's Footballer of the Year for a record-extending sixth time. The 34-year-old striker, who has been in peak form in the last couple of years, has earlier won the honour in 2007, 2011, 2013, 2014 and 2017. He currently plays for Bengaluru FC in the Indian Super League.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70148029,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-190244,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562687909]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[$30 billion wiped off India stocks as tax clarity eludes market]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/30-billion-wiped-off-india-stocks-as-tax-clarity-eludes-market/articleshow/70147972.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[By Ameya KarveIt’s an old saw of India’s budget documents -- the devil lies in details of the fine print.A higher surcharge on wealthy Indians in the budget has spooked non-resident and overseas funds enough to erase 2.3 trillion rupees ($30 billion) in market value from companies in the S&P BSE Sensex over the past three sessions.The reason: the realization that the new tax rate applies not just to the super rich but also to trusts -- a structure of choice for a large number of foreign funds that invest in the nation.The proposal “seems to have inadvertently” dragged foreign portfolio investors into the tax net and must be clarified by the government, said K.R. Sekar, a partner at Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu India LLP.Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman in her budget speech Friday proposed to increase the surcharge from 15% to 25% for those with taxable incomes of between 20 million rupees and 50 million rupees, and to 37% for those earning more than 50 million rupees. This takes the effective tax rate for those two groups to 39% and 42.74%, respectively.Global and non-resident investors participate in India via non-corporate trusts and the so-called association of persons. Problem is, the structures are treated on par with individuals for tax purposes. That has stoked concerns about the levy encompassing foreigners at a time when the nation has emerged as Asia’s biggest destination for equity money in 2019.“An investment vehicle -- such as a category III alternative investment or an FPI -- taxed at a fund level is likely to get affected as the income may easily exceed 50 million rupees,” said Vaibhav Sanghavi, co-chief executive officer at Avendus Capital PBC Markets Alternate Strategies LLP in Mumbai. Alternative investments, such as hedge funds, which use complex trading strategies, are classified as category III by the markets regulator.The head of the nation’s direct-tax department Monday said the government would clarify on the applicability of the higher levy on global investors. But a few hours later, Sitharaman ruled out an immediate clarification.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70147972/30-billion-wiped-off-india-stocks-as-tax-clarity-eludes-market.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562687624]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Doubts over Deutsche Bank turnaround plan dent shaky shares]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/9cMn5nHaunY/doubts-over-deutsche-bank-turnaround-plan-dent-shaky-shares-idINKCN1U30A1]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank shares extended losses on Tuesday on investor doubts that its chief executive can revive the lender by shrinking the investment bank and returning to its roots as banker to corporate Germany.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406069421&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680JR]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562687228]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019 Semi Final, India vs New Zealand: Rain Interrupts Play At Old Trafford]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-manchester-weather-report-2066462]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In case of a wash out, the semi-final match between India and New Zealand will be played on the reserve day.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/dtq88juo_rain-_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562686423]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Wimbledon witnesses first 12-12 tiebreak]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/wimbledon-witnesses-first-12-12-tiebreak/articleshow/70147184.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wimbledon got its first 12-12 final set tie-break on Tuesday when Henri Kontinen and John Peers defeated Rajeev Ram and Joe Salisbury in a men's doubles match. The eighth-seeded pair won 7-6 (7/2), 6-4, 3-6, 4-6, 13-12 (7/2) in four hours and 29 minutes.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70147434,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-181710,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562685837]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA["My Life Is Now Sorted": Michael Vaughan Tweets After Being Blocked By Sanjay Manjrekar]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-michael-vaughan-gets-blocked-by-sanjay-manjrekar-tweets-my-life-is-now-sorted-2066910]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Michael Vaughan and Sanjay Manjrekar were involved in a verbal spat after the latter's "bits and pieces" remarks about Ravindra Jadeja.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/r6p57mq_michael-vaughan_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562684594]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[NRIs to be taxed for receiving gifts from Indians]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/news/economy/policy/budget-extends-tax-on-nris-for-receiving-gifts-from-resident-indians/articleshow/70147065.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI: The expensive gift that you kept for your overseas cousin or friend may attract tax from this year with the Budget 2019-20 proposing to impose withholding tax all such transfers, plugging an earlier loophole that allowed its tax- free treatment.The Finance Bill 2019 has imposed tax on any sum of money paid or any property situated in India, transferred by a person resident in India to a person outside India, as it would be deemed to accrue or arise in India. The changes will be applied for all such transfers made on or after July 5, 2019.Currently gifts given by Indian residents to non-resident Indians - apart from the specified list of relatives - would be claimed as non-taxable. This is because the earlier tax put the onus on the recipient of the gift to make the disclosure and pay tax. As a gift to NRIs means that income is accrued abroad, it remained outside the tax net.But now, all gifts to NRIs will be income accruing in India and would be taxed as per the normal slab rates applicable to resident Indians. This means that the origin of the gift becomes important for tax purpose, instead of the destination of the gift abroad.The onus will be on the recipient (the NRI in this case) of the gift to disclose such gifts received if they originate in India and then pay a tax on it.So, if the value of the gift is above Rs 10 lakh, the recipient will have to pay 30 per cent tax. The tax rate would get higher if the value of the gift, be it payment for studies or a house abroad, is more than Rs 2 crore or Rs 5 crore. In such cases, the highest tax rate for super rich, i.e. 35.7 and 42.7 per cent respectively would apply.For the purpose, gift will constitute shares, property, vouchers, cash etc exceeding Rs 50,000 made to anyone, apart from the specified relatives or blood relations.While making gifts to NRIs taxable, the Budget has proposed that in a treaty situation, the relevant article of applicable DTAA (double taxation avoidance treaty) shall continue to apply for such gifts as well.This amendment will take effect from April 1, 2020 and will, apply in relation to the assessment year 2020-21 and subsequent assessment years.The specified relatives list in terms of Section 56 of the Income Tax Act is fairly wide. It includes brothers and sisters, and their spouses. Gifts to this category will not attract any tax. But acquaintances, friends, and other close family relations would come under the purview of the tax.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70147065/nris-to-be-taxed-for-receiving-gifts-from-indians.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562684185]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Serena into 12th Wimbledon semi-final after tough duel]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/serena-into-12th-wimbledon-semi-final-after-tough-duel/articleshow/70146975.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Seven-time champion Serena Williams reached her 12th Wimbledon semi-final on Tuesday with a hard fought 6-4, 4-6, 6-3 victory over unseeded American compatriot Alison Riske.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70146987,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1632998,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562683627]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[As waters warm, lionfish invasion strains Lebanon's seas]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/b6-lAtVpT8g/as-waters-warm-lionfish-invasion-strains-lebanons-seas-idINKCN1U41P9]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lebanese fisherman Hassan Younes has been diving the same waters off his coastal hometown for three decades but has never seen anything like this year as native species disappear and invasive lionfish take their place.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406156048&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF68144]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562683169]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Coin fails to land on either side during toss in Nepal vs Hong Kong U19 match]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/news/coin-fails-to-land-on-either-side-during-toss-in-nepal-vs-hong-kong-u19-match/articleshow/70146672.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a bizarre turn of events, the toss during the Nepal vs Hong Kong ACC U19 - Eastern Region - 2019 final had to be redone after the coin failed to land on either side and instead stood upright. ]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70146683,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1258021,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562682593]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019: Liam Plunkett Warns Australia: England Are A 'Different Animal' Now]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/australia-vs-england-liam-plunkett-warns-australia-england-are-a-different-animal-now-2066903]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Liam Plunkett warns Australia that England are a "different sort of animal" from their predecessors as they prepare for their blockbuster World Cup semi-final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/hl8ajrqo_liam-plunkett-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562682432]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Arun Kumar appointed as DGCA chief]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/industry/transportation/airlines-/-aviation/arun-kumar-appointed-as-dgca-chief/articleshow/70146670.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI: Arun Kumar, additional secretary in the Ministry of Civil Aviation, will now be holding the full-time charge of the head of aviation regulator DGCA, an official order said Tuesday. "The Appointments Committee of the Cabinet has approved the appointment of Arun Kumar, Additional Secretary and Financial Advisor, Ministry of Civil Aviation as Director General in the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) in the rank and pay of Additional Secretary," said the order issued by the Department of Personnel and Training. Kumar was heading the DGCA as an additional charge between May 31 and July 9 this year. Kumar is an IAS officer of 1989 batch of Haryana cadre. Before Kumar, B S Bhullar was holding the full-time charge of DGCA chief. Bhullar, an IAS officer of Uttar Pradesh cadre, was appointed as full-time DGCA chief in December 2016. In between June 2016 and December 2016, Bhullar was heading the DGCA as additional charge. In this time period, his main role was as additional secretary in the Ministry of Civil Aviation.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70146670/arun-kumar-appointed-as-dgca-chief.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562682094]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Hope god sits in our dressing room if we play England in final: Shastri]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/hope-god-sits-in-our-dressing-room-if-we-play-england-in-final-ravi-shastri/articleshow/70146577.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India coach Ravi Shastri felt god was in England's dressing room during their World Cup league stage loss to the hosts, but hoped he will be on their side if they meet again, in the tournament final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70146564,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1672116,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562681907]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Apple Refreshes the MacBook Air, MacBook Pro Ahead of Back-to-School Season]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/laptops/news/macbook-air-2019-price-in-india-13-inch-pro-launch-specifications-2066897]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-Retina MacBook Air, Non-Touch Bar MacBook Pro, 12-inch MacBook are all gone.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/macbook_air_true_tone_1562681287594.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562681323]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rupee could be staring at a new threat]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/nri/nri-investments/about-94-billion-worth-nri-deposits-come-up-for-maturity-in-fy20/articleshow/70146490.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[MUMBAI: The Indian Rupee is staring at a shaky year ahead as nearly $94 billion of Non Resident Indians' deposits mature. While all deposits may not leave the shores, some could go back given the narrowing of interest advantage that India had over the West. Given that short term deposits of NRI have been gaining over long term deposits, the fall in interest rates may play a significant role.According to the latest external debt figures released by the Reserve Bank of India for FY’19, of the total NRI deposits worth $130.4 billion, deposits worth $94 billion are going to come up for maturity in the current fiscal year. The figure looks alarmists, but about 90 per cent of such deposits gets rolled over, according to currency market analysts at both banks and other authorised dealers of foreign currency.But what could be a cause of concern is the share of such of such short-term NRI deposits in total NRI deposits is slowly rising. The share of NRI deposits maturing within a year has gone up from 51 per cent in March 2015 to 72 per cent in March 2019.Experts attribute this trend to higher returns on short-term deposits in the Indian markets. “ This is largely attributed to the inverted yield curve that has emerged in India for over a year now “ said K N De, managing partner at United Financial Consultants. “ As a result, short-term interest rates are higher than long term rates and this has made short-term rates more attractive for the global Indians.”Also, the Indian diaspora could be looking at more attractive opportunities with more reforms expected by the new government, according to a senior treasury official with a local bank.NRIs have been parking their funds in Indian banks largely due to the wide interest rate differential between their country of residence and their country of origin and enjoying on the interest rate advantage. They have option of parking in two kinds of repatriable deposits. FCNR (B) or foreign currency non-resident (banks), where the currency risk is borne by the bank and NRE (RA) or non-resident external -rupee account, where the foreign currency risk is borne by the depositer.The mix of these kind of deposits as far the investment preference is concerned often depends on the trend in currency movements. Investments in NRE deposits tend to spurt whenever, investors take a view that the rupee will appreciate over the term of the deposits so that the investors also gains on currency movement in addition to the interest rate he earns on the deposit.But interest rates are expected to fall in future with the Indian central bank signalling an accommodative monetary policy and hence interest differential for the NRI may not remain as attractive in the past.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70146490/rupee-could-be-staring-at-a-new-threat.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562681305]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Defence is the best form of attack, says Fergus Kavanagh]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/hockey/top-stories/defence-is-the-best-form-of-attack-says-fergus-kavanagh/articleshow/70146453.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a year to go for the Tokyo Olympics, the Indian men's hockey team is far from being a finished product. To begin with, it must cross the first and critical hurdle of qualifying for the Games. To up their game, Manpreet Singh's men have been going through specialized position-based training camps over the past couple of months.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70146433,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1130992,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562681186]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[AI-powered storage company enters Northeast market with “front-of-the-meter” solution]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/RenewableEnergyNewsRssFeed/~3/pBu4X8RQvn0/aipowered-storage-company-enters-northeast-market-with-frontofthemeter-solution.html]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[This week artificial intelligence (AI)-driven energy storage services provider Stem said that it had formed a partnership with New York-based private equity company Syncarpha Capital to build 28.2 megawatt-hours (MWh) of large-scale storage projects co-sited with solar in Massachusetts.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Power]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562681168]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Halep beats Zhang to reach Wimbledon semifinals]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/halep-beats-zhang-to-reach-wimbledon-semifinals/articleshow/70146150.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simona Halep reached her second Wimbledon semi-final on Tuesday with a 7-6 (7/4), 6-1 victory over China's Zhang Shuai.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70146364,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1348388,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562680868]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semi-Final: Michael Vaughan Continues To Troll Sanjay Manjrekar For "Bits and Pieces" Remark]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-michael-vaughan-continues-to-troll-sanjay-manjrekar-for-bits-and-pieces-remark-2066809]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sanjay Manjrekar has been facing a lot of criticism for his remarks on Ravindra Jadeja.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/4sagvv1o_ravindra-jadeja-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562680698]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Calls for justice, intervention as Philippines buries drug war's youngest known victim]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/nOFqdJg2Gqs/calls-for-justice-intervention-as-philippines-buries-drug-wars-youngest-known-victim-idINKCN1U41FK]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[One by one, a mother and her children splash holy water over a white coffin barely a metre long. On the dirt floor beneath it lies a pair of tiny pink slippers.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406130170&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680WD]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562680446]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Micromax Launches 'Google-Certified' Android TV Lineup in India]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/tv/news/micromax-android-tv-price-in-india-rs-13999-release-date-july-11-flipkart-2066886]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Micromax's new Android TV lineup will go on sale in India from Thursday, July 11, via Flipkart.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/micromax_android_tv_1562679967634.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562680179]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Redmi K20, Redmi K20 Pro Get Mi CC9's Sky Replacement Feature]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/xiaomi-redmi-k20-pro-get-sky-filter-first-introduced-on-mi-cc9-cc9e-2066882]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Redmi General Manager Lu Weibing took to Weibo to announce that the 'Sky' filter is rolling out for Redmi K20 and Redmi K20 Pro users.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/redmik20_main_1562679857246.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562679897]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semi Final: Mohammed Shami's Coach Slams Decision To Bench Fast Bowler]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-mohammed-shamis-coach-slams-decision-to-bench-the-fast-bowler-2066875]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mohammed Shami has taken 14 wickets in just four outings in World Cup 2019, including a hat-trick.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/eqq1d3tg_mohammed-shami-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562679718]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Plunkett warns Australia: England are a 'different animal' now]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/plunkett-warns-australia-england-are-a-different-animal-now/articleshow/70145952.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Liam Plunkett has warned Australia that England are a "different sort of animal" from their predecessors as they prepare for their blockbuster World Cup semi-final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70145921,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1715615,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562679109]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Airtel's Rs. 97 Recharge Offers 2GB Data, Unlimited Calls for 14 Days]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/telecom/news/airtel-rs-97-prepaid-recharge-plan-2gb-data-unlimited-calls-100-sms-benefits-14-days-validity-2066872]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rs. 97 Airtel prepaid recharge plan brings 2GB data, unlimited voice calls, and 100 SMS messages per day for 14 days.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/airtel_logo_reuters_1559712972320.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562678981]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Asus Launches New ROG Gaming Laptop, Desktop Lineups in India]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/laptops/news/asus-rog-zephyrus-m-gu502-strix-scar-iii-hero-g-huracan-desktops-india-launched-price-specifications-2066871]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The additions to ROG Strix range comes with the world's fastest 240Hz 3ms gaming laptop display.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/asuszephyrusm_main1_1562678903423.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562678916]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[SJVN, BHEL in MoU for solar projects]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/industry/energy/power/sjvn-bhel-in-mou-for-solar-projects/articleshow/70145778.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[NEW DELHI: SJVN Ltd on Tuesday said it has entered into a MoU with Bharat Heavy Electrical Ltd for development of solar power projects in India. The MoU aims at building a strategic partnership between the parties for jointly pursuing commercial solar power projects through participation in tariff/viability gap funding based competitive bidding process.As per MoU, BHEL will be an engineering, procurement, construction and project management contractor for SJVN projects. In addition to this, BHEL will also provide operation and maintenance services after commissioning of project. SJVN Ltd has commissioned five projects totalling 2015.2 mw of installed capacity including solar and wind. The company is presently implementing power projects in Himachal Pradesh, Uttarakhand, Bihar, Maharashtra and Gujarat in India besides neighbouring countries viz. Nepal and Bhutan. This is one of steps for SJVN towards becoming 5000 mw company by 2023, and 25000 mw by 2040.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70145778/sjvn-bhel-in-mou-for-solar-projects.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562678530]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Even 'paan ki dukaan' is better run: Feud at IndiGo gets murkier]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/stocks/news/indigo-promoters-feud-takes-serious-turn-gangwal-seeks-sebis-intervention/articleshow/70145629.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[MUMBAI: The simmering feud between the IndiGo promoters took a turn for the worse on Tuesday after one of the warring partners complained to the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) about questionable corporate governance practices, alleging that even a `paan ki dukaan’ would have handled things better. Rakesh Gangwal, who holds 37% in IndiGo compared with co-promoter turned rival Rahul Bhatia’s 38%, said in his complaint to the market regulator that a shareholders’ agreement between himself and Bhatia gave the latter “unusual controlling rights over IndiGo” and that these rights and “a lack of diversity and paucity” of independent directors “may very well be at the root of why governance matters have taken such a back seat at IndiGo”. ET on May 17 reported the agreement skewed in favour of Bhatia was at the root of the conflict between the founders.In his letter, Gangwal alleged that over the years, Bhatia began “building an ecosystem of other companies that would enter into dozens of related party transactions with IndiGo.”The letter was also sent to Prime Minister Narendra Modi, finance minister Nirmala Sitharaman and commerce minister Piyush Goyal, apart from aviation minister Hardeep Puri and aviation regulator Arun Kumar.
    
    70146342





In a separate letter to the board, Mr Gangwal has alleged that various related party transactions with the IGE Group were executed without seeking audit committee approval and many were executed without seeking competitive bids from third parties. He said many had been signed with retrospective effect (back dated).He cited the example of IndiGo’s office spaces always rented from IGE Group companies. This year, when the lease expired, IndiGo again chose an IGE Group company for its office space.However, instead of the lease rates logically increasing at renewal, the new lease rates going forward were lower by more than 25%.“To the best of our knowledge such competitive bidding was not entered into when the original lease agreement was entered into with the IGE Group entities years ago,” alleged Gangwal.Gangwal’s missive is bound to increase scrutiny of IndiGo’s practices by the market regulator and by other government agencies and marks yet another unhappy, unfortunate milestone for the country’s aviation sector, buffeted by headwinds such as the collapse of Jet Airways. Speaking to ET, Gangwal confirmed the widening gulf between the two promoters on corporate governance issues. “This is a national issue where some companies have lost their moral compass of governance and the nation needs to address this issue formally," Gangwal said.India’s biggest airline by market share shared the letters in a filing on the Bombay Stock Exchange. Rahul Bhatia, of the IGE group, the other co-founder could not be reached for his comments.Bhatia’s affiliate IGE Group has the right to appoint three out of six directors at the airline, nominate the chairman of the board, nominate and appoint the managing director, the CEO and the president.Gangwal said his affiliate had requisitioned in May an extraordinary general meeting to be held the following month which the board didn’t allow in a split vote. He said the board also refused to cooperate and provide the necessary information for the requisitionists (Gangwal and his affiliates) to conduct the EGM themselves despite this right being available under law.“We believe that this whole set of events goes far beyond just poor governance and even a "paan ki dukaan" would have handled these matters with more grace,” he said in his letter to shareholders.In his response to the requisition for an EGM to point out the related party transactions, Bhatia called Gangwal’s stand “false, frivolous, and misleading”. Bhatia alleged that the “real agenda of the RG (Rakesh Gangwal) Group was “to dilute and diminish the controlling rights of the IGE Group and to relieve itself from its obligations under the Shareholders' Agreement ("SHA") and the Articles of Association ("AoA") which ensure implementation and enforcement of the IGE Group's controlling rights”Bhatia called the “red herring issue of related party transactions is nothing more than a publicity seeking device to attempt to tarnish the reputation of the IGE Group and to position the RG Group as a saviour of the Company against alleged pillaging by the IGE Group,”Bhatia said Gangwal didn’t raise “for 13 years a whisper against” the related party transactions. He also said the value of the transactions was less than 1% of the consolidated turnover of the company.Gangwal said he ultimately will make the company hold the EGM to shed light on the related party transactions. Gangwal said that while IndiGo has always appointed an “independent chairman” the right given to Bhatia to appoint a chairman defeats the purpose. He said the IGE Group always nominates a single person as chairman and that person is appointed. He called the process “Hobson’s choice” usually referring to choosing what’s available or nothing at all. He alleged this was a way of “circumventing SEBI rules”.Gangwal said that while most of the provisions in the agreement expires in November, the rights skewed in favour of Bhatia are part of the articles of association and will continue post November.“I request SEBI to look into and, if thought fit, ask the company to make necessary changes to the unusual controlling rights available to the IGE Group, a minority shareholder with about 38% shareholding,” Gangwal said in his letter.“I have vigorously attempted for almost a year to persuade the company to shore up its governance standards and all my attempts have been thwarted by the IGE Group,” said Gangwal. He mentioned “whistleblowers who had the courage and wisdom to send information that allowed for this pursuit of almost a year.”Here is the full text of the letter: Dear Mr. Tyagi, Mr. Mahalingam, Mr. Baiwar and Mr. Sundaresan,July 8, 2019I am a co-founder and a director of lnterGiobe Aviation Limited (Company or IndiGo), a company listed on the Bombay Stock Exchange and National Stock Exchange and along with my affiliates hold approximately 37% share holding in the Company. Mr. Rahul Bhatia, also a co-founder and a director of IndiGo, along with his affiliates (IGE Group) owns almost equal shareholding of approximately 38%. And, a little more than 25% shareholding ofthe Company is widely held by public shareholders which includes retail shareholders and some of the most well-regarded, marquee, global investors and funds.IndiGo was founded with the objective of creating an airline to serve the people of India with a world class product and built on foundations of transparency, uncompromising values and principles. The hard work of the employees of IndiGo has paid off. Now, IndiGo is one of the most successful aviation companies in the world and not just in India. However, today, IndiGo is at a watershed moment. It has started veering off from the core principles and values of governance that made IndiGo what it is today. Having spent more than 30 years working in and leading some of the most reputed airlines in the world, including United Airlines, Air France, and US Airways, I decided to join hands with Mr. Bhatia, a longtime friend, to build a large air transportation network in India that would make the nation proud.Rooted from a deep trust built over a decade long friendship and with no desire on my part to have any meaningful control of the Company, I entered into a shareholders' agreement that allows Mr. Bhatia unusual controlling rights over IndiGo. Mr. Bhatia has the right (i) to appoint 3 out of 6 directors of IndiGo; (ii) that requires that "The Chairman of the Board shall be appointed on the nomination of the IGE Group ... " ; (iii) to nominate and appoint the Managing Director, (iv) to nominate and appoint the CEO; and (v) to nominate and appoint the President. These controlling rights give IGE Group, a minority shareholder, significant influence over the decisions of IndiGo and there is nothing wrong in that by itself, provided such influence is used judiciously and with prudence and is in the best interest of the Company. I hadn't contemplated that over the years, Mr. Bhatia would start building an ecosystem of other companies that would enter into dozens of related party transactions with IndiGo. We are not against RPTs as long as proper checks and balances exist and such RPTs are in the best interest of the Company.Beyond just questionable RPTs, various fundamental governance norms and laws are not being adhered to and this is inevitably going to lead to unfortunate outcomes, unless effective measures are taken today.Allow me to bring to your attention some of the events that demonstrate the collapsing corporate governance standards at IndiGo. These run the gamut of:• Violations of various corporate governance regulations prescribed by SEBI and violations of the Company's Code of Conduct for Directors and Senior Management.• In a split vote, the Board taking the decision to not allow an Extraordinary General Meeting of shareholders (EGM) upon being requisitioned by shareholders with approximately 37% of shareholding in the Company and also refusing to cooperate and provide the necessary information for the requisitionists to conduct the EGM themselves despite this right being available under law.• Board decisions and resolutions on critical matters being implemented without basic governance protocols and laws being followed.• Significantly diminishing and taking away the authority vested by SEBI to the Nomination and Remuneration Committee (NRC} for identifying persons who may be appointed in senior management. This was done by pushing through a Board resolution that now gives IGE Group the right to identify and screen the candidates for Managing Director, the Chief Executive Officer and the President of the Company. And, also the right to propose to the NRC the appointment, the job profile, qualifications and remuneration of such candidates and require the Company's HR organization to provide all necessary support to the IGE Group on these matters.• IndiGo has since its inception had an "independent director" as its Chairman. However, the provision in the articles of association stating "The Chairman of the Board shall be appointed on the nomination of the IGE Group ... " has the real potential to take away the independence of the Chairman. It has been a common practice at IndiGo that IGE Group nominates or "recommends" a single person for appointment as IndiGo's Chairman and, from this candidate pool of only one person, that individual is then appointed and designated as an "independent director". While, we aren't questioning the independence of the current Chairman in his decision making, we are questioning the designation of such an individual as "independent". This process of appointing an "independent Chairman" at IndiGo is the classic "Hobson's choice" and a sophisticated way to circumvent SEBI rules and avoid the requirement of designating such a Chairman as nonindependent which would then have required IndiGo to have a majority of Directors to be independent. It simply does not meet the requirements and spirit of the regulations prescribed by SEBI.• Not having appointed an independent woman director, a requirement that SEBI gave time to the Company since May 2018 to comply.The unusual rights available to the IGE Group in conjunction with the lack of diversity and paucity of independent directors in the Board may very well be at the root of why governance matters have taken such a back seat at IndiGo. I request SEBI to look into and, if thought fit, ask the Company to make necessary changes to the unusual controlling rights available to the IGE Group, a minority shareholder with about 38% shareholding. These unusual rights survive even after this coming November when most of the provisions of the current shareholders agreement expire, since, these rights remain embedded in the articles of association of IndiGo and will continue to survive unless the articles are amended by a vote of shareholders holding more than 75% shares.These rights are:• right to appoint 3 out of 6 directors of IndiGo.• "The Chairman of the Board shall be appointed on the nomination of the IGE Group ... "• right to nominate and appoint the Managing Director.• right to nominate and appoint the CEO.• right to nominate and appoint the President.• a voting arrangement that requires me and my affiliates to vote alongside the IGE Group on the appointment of Directors.In the past, Mr. Bhatia has argued that these rights flow from the shareholders' agreement and were disclosed in the prospectus at the time of IndiGo's IPO in 2015. However, times, circumstances and behavior of promoters have changed since 2015. Also, now, SEBI has rightly taken certain positions on these matters and most of these rights are not in accordance with SEBI regulations. Such unusual rights for a minority shareholder needs a fresh look in light of the facts that IndiGo is now a critical national asset, serves almost 50% of the domestic air travelers, the aviation industry in India has regrettably experienced a checkered and difficult financial history and, especially, in the context that these unusual controlling rights seem to be the basis for the various violations of law and governance at IndiGo. The nation can illafford IndiGo to ever falter.Attached are letters that we intend to ultimately send to all our shareholders and hold an EGM and shed additional light on RPTs that the IGE Group has engaged in with the Company. These letters stand on their own merits and spell out in detail various governance failures. It is well known that quite a few prominent and important Indian companies have faltered due to, amongst other reasons, lax adherence to corporate governance and weak Board oversight. It is imperative that IndiGo has the confidence of the travelling public, its employees, the shareholders and the various government entities and officials by adhering to the highest level of corporate governance and transparency. We are big believers in the long-term potential of IndiGo and its business and operational model. However, we also firmly believe that IndiGo can only realise its true potential and be a world class company if it has both- a world class business and operational model as well as world class governance standards Under a separate letter to yourselves, my counsel, Khaitan & Co, have highlighted numerous transgressions by Board members, the IGE Group and the Company that defy governance protocols and flout various SEBI Regulations. In that letter, Khaitan & Co are also providing you numerous troubling Company emails, reports and other material which by themselves establish the facts and list out the various violations of SEBI Regulations and corporate governance.I have vigorously attempted for almost a year to persuade the Company to shore up its governance standards, and all my attempts have been thwarted by the IGE Group. The Company's and certain Board members constant platitudes that they are "working on these issues ... going forward we will be more mindful ... we have been addressing these issues" have become just words. I am now constrained to seek SEBI's intervention to direct the Company to amend its articles of association to comply with SEBI  Regulations, to strictly follow the requirements prescribed by SEBI in letter and in spirit on Board matters and proceedings and to direct the Company to allow for the EGM resolution to be placed in front of all the shareholders of the Company.We are grateful to all the whistle blowers who had the courage and wisdom to send information that allowed for this pursuit of almost a year. Without that information it may not have been possible to uncover some of the specifics and facts that formed the basis for the EGM requisition.Understandably, this issue will become a topic of widespread national discussion, misinformation, speculation or worse. In fact, some of this has started to manifest itself in various media reports and Company management being less than forthcoming in its statements by down playing the underlying issues. To allay any concerns among various governmental authorities, our customers, our employees and our shareholders that the operations of IndiGo are not impacted or disrupted and, equally importantly, to keep such public and private discourse to the facts, we are sending copies of this letter and its attachments to various regulatory and other entities. However, recognizing the confidential and sensitive nature of the information, the letter being sent under separate cover by my counsel, including the attachments and information sources, is only being submitted to SEBI.In closing, we recognize that there are influential and powerful people on the Company's Board who will use their position to influence the outcome of the campaign that the RG Group has embarked upon. Their biggest arguments to downplay the issues will be that these are minor "procedural irregularities" and the Company is addressing them. However, we take comfort in the fact that no one is above the law and India is changing for the better. Also, we would like to point out that other retail shareholders, promoters or institutional investors may also face similar issues with other errant, publicly listed companies. Either they do not have the means and resources or lack the internal knowledge and workings of the company to be able to take effective steps to correct the wrongs and, hence, resign themselves to such errant corporate behavior. We believe that our cause is in the larger national interest and not just because of the relevance of IndiGo to the nation. This is a landmark issue and SEBI has the ability to send a clear message to all errant companies to adhere to the spirit and intent of the regulations. Confidence and effective functioning of capital markets is anchored on such principles. Sincerely,Rakesh Gangwal]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70145629/even-paan-ki-dukaan-is-better-run-feud-at-indigo-gets-murkier.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562677967]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Logitech Wireless Keyboards, Mice Vulnerable to Hijacking Flaws: Report]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/laptops/news/logitech-wireless-keyboard-vulnerabilities-unifying-tech-mice-marcus-mengs-2066856]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A security researcher has found vulnerabilities in the USB receivers used by Logitech wireless keyboard, mice, and presentation clickers. These vulnerabilities can allow a malicious party to not only...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/logitech_dongle_g360_1562677658158.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562677777]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[England have positive record against Australia: Joe Root]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/world-cup-2019-england-have-positive-record-against-australia-in-last-four-years-says-joe-root/articleshow/70145489.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[England's star batsman Joe Root says they have the ability to exact revenge for the league stage loss to Australia when the arch-rivals meet in Thursday's World Cup semifinal.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70145563,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1108686,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562677775]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Access denied? Not really if you use Android]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/software/over-1k-android-apps-gain-your-data-even-if-denied-permission/articleshow/70145476.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO: Researchers from the International Computer Science Institute (ICSI) in the US identified 1,325 Android apps that were gathering data from devices even after people explicitly denied them permission, news portal CNET reported on Tuesday.Serge Egelman, Director of Usable Security And Privacy research at the ICSI, presented the study at the Federal Trade Commission's privacy conference.He said the researchers had notified Google about these issues in September 2018, as well as the FTC.One of the apps mentioned by name was Shutterfly, which is used for editing photos. It had been gathering GPS coordinates from photos and sending that data to its own servers.In a statement, Shutterfly said: "Like many photo services, Shutterfly uses this data to enhance the user experience with features such as categorization and personalized product suggestions, all in accordance with Shutterfly's privacy policy as well as the Android developer agreement."The study published on the FTC website cited 153 apps, including Samsung's Health and Browser apps, which are installed in more than 500 million devices.According to the report, Egelman would be presenting more detailed information about the research findings at the Usenix Security conference in August. ]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70145476/access-denied-not-really-if-you-use-android.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562677390]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Over 1k Android apps gain your data even if denied permission]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/tech/software/over-1k-android-apps-gain-your-data-even-if-denied-permission/articleshow/70145476.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO: Researchers from the International Computer Science Institute (ICSI) in the US identified 1,325 Android apps that were gathering data from devices even after people explicitly denied them permission, news portal CNET reported on Tuesday.Serge Egelman, Director of Usable Security And Privacy research at the ICSI, presented the study at the Federal Trade Commission's privacy conference.He said the researchers had notified Google about these issues in September 2018, as well as the FTC.One of the apps mentioned by name was Shutterfly, which is used for editing photos. It had been gathering GPS coordinates from photos and sending that data to its own servers.In a statement, Shutterfly said: "Like many photo services, Shutterfly uses this data to enhance the user experience with features such as categorization and personalized product suggestions, all in accordance with Shutterfly's privacy policy as well as the Android developer agreement."The study published on the FTC website cited 153 apps, including Samsung's Health and Browser apps, which are installed in more than 500 million devices.According to the report, Egelman would be presenting more detailed information about the research findings at the Usenix Security conference in August. ]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70145476/over-1k-android-apps-gain-your-data-even-if-denied-permission.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562677390]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Thousands of Android Apps Can Track You Without Your Permission: Study]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/apps/news/android-apps-tracking-without-permissions-privacycon-google-play-android-q-2066852]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are thousands of Android apps that have found ways to gather information like device Mac address, location, phone's IMEI, and more even if they don't have necessary permissions to access...]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/google_android_reuters_1557489952979.JPG]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562677328]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ACT Fibernet Offers 100GB Extra Data to Celebrate Cricket World Cup]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/telecom/news/act-fibernet-100gb-additional-data-icc-cricket-world-cup-2019-2066839]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[ACT Fibernet is celebrating the ICC Cricket World Cup 2019 by offering 100GB additional data to all its customers across India.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/act_fibernet_new_brand_logo_gadgets_360_1562676395474.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562676486]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Hardik Pandya Faces Injury Scare During India vs New Zealand World Cup Semi-Final]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-hardik-pandya-injury-scare-2066824]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hardik Pandya pulled up during his first bowling spell in the World Cup 2019 semi-final against New Zealand but returned to the field after spending a little time in the dressing room.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/q6m1uivg_hardik-pandya-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562675705]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Playing video games can make you more creative: Study]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/more-lifestyle/playing-video-games-can-make-you-more-creative-study/story-Aepj9eoF4usRybti3STkbI.html]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent study published in the Creativity Research Journal claims that games like Minecraft encourage players to practice some level of creativity.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://www.hindustantimes.com/rf/image_size_960x540/HT/p2/2019/07/09/Pictures/_8ca1be4a-a240-11e9-85f3-0f8400bbe260.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562675601]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[PSG Get Tough With Neymar After Pre-Season No-Show]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/football/psg-get-tough-with-neymar-after-pre-season-no-show-2066832]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neymar, the world's most expensive player after moving to PSG for 222 million euros ($252 million), had watched his country win the Copa America.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/j2b6v818_neymar-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562675568]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sam Querrey hoping he doesn't 'get clock cleaned' by Rafael Nadal]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/sam-querrey-hoping-he-doesnt-get-clock-cleaned-by-rafael-nadal/articleshow/70144976.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sam Querrey will try to take down Rafael Nadal at Wimbledon on Wednesday but if it all goes belly-up, the big American just hopes he doesn't get his 'clock cleaned'.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70144997,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-197051,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562675337]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Facebook US Data Transfer Case Goes to Europe's Top Court]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/social-networking/news/facebook-max-schrems-us-data-transfer-case-european-court-of-justice-july-9-2066823]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[An Austrian privacy campaigner's long-running legal battle against Facebook over its data transfers to the US reached the European Union's highest court on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/facebook_reuters_1557900601740.JPG]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562674912]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Fans express love for MS Dhoni and Virat Kohli]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/india-vs-new-zealand-fans-express-love-for-ms-dhoni-and-virat-kohli/articleshow/70144588.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the Old Trafford turned blue in support of India against New Zealand at the ICC Men's Cricket World Cup semi-final on Tuesday, the fans expressed their love and respect for both current and former captain, Virat Kohli and MS Dhoni.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70144705,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1705895,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562674491]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Some jobs to be hit in India as well due to global lay-off: Deutsche]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/industry/banking/finance/some-jobs-to-be-hit-in-india-as-well-due-to-global-lay-off-deutsche/articleshow/70144614.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mumbai: Deutsche Bank India Tuesday said the decision of the German parent to lay off as many as 18,000 employees globally will have an impact here as well, but declined to quantify the number of employees who will be hit. The largest German lender over the weekend had announced shuttering of its global equities business and cutting fixed income operations, which will impact as many as 18,000 jobs globally while help the bank save USD 8.3 billion annually. "The equity desk will be shut for sure in India as well. There is no ambiguity around it. This has jobs in trading, research and sales," a source told . The situation was described as "fluid" with no clarity on the number of jobs impacted here, or if the impacted employees will be accommodated in other operations of the bank, which has 17 branches in the country. The domestic equity business was termed as "very small" in the global equity business. According to industry sources, a foreign bank usually employees 25-35 in its institutional equities businesses. However, there can be other employees serving global markets through the its offshore global delivery centres in the country which can also be impacted. A bank spokesperson told that "it is too early to comment on the specifics. We will be communicating directly with our employees regarding their jobs and options available to them." The spokesperson further said such decisions have a "profound" impact on people's lives. "That is why we will do whatever we can to be as responsible and sensitive as possible when implementing these changes," the spokesperson said. Experts said there is a process which will have to be monitored by regulators while undertaking an operation like shutting down a business. The official also drew attention to the capital release unit housing assets worth over 160 billion euros being created.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70144614/some-jobs-to-be-hit-in-india-as-well-due-to-global-lay-off-deutsche.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562673962]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Realme 3 Pro Discounts, Realme C2 Warranty Offer Announced for New Sale]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/realme-c2-3-pro-million-days-sale-two-year-warranty-price-cut-details-2066807]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As part of this sale, the company will offer two-year warranty on the Realme C2 and a temporary price drop of the Realme 3 Pro.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/realme_c2_1555920812378.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562673759]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[EON switches all U.K. customers to 100% renewable power]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/RenewableEnergyNewsRssFeed/~3/p0jNcIGwLrQ/eon-switches-all-uk-customers-to-100-renewable-power.html]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[EON SE is now supplying all of its 3.3 million residential customers in Britain with 100% renewable electricity, the first of the U.K.’s “Big Six” utilities to do so.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Power]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562673684]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Honor 9X Pro Schematics Leaked, Tip Pop-Up Selfie Camera]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/honor-9x-pro-schematics-leak-ahead-of-china-launch-2066800]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Honor 9X Pro Schematics Leak ahead of July 23 China launch]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/Honor_9X_Pro_NDTV_Cover_1562673362711.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562673671]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Hotstar Telecast Interrupted Repeatedly]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/apps/news/india-vs-new-zealand-hotstar-down-live-streaming-interrupted-due-to-technical-failure-2066795]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hotstar's India vs New Zealand World Cup match stream is experiencing intermittent technical problems, leaving millions of Hotstar subscribers without an avenue to watch the cricket match.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/hotstar_ind_nz_interupption_gadgets_360_1562672500715.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562673462]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Amit Panghal to spearhead India's challenge at World Championships]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/boxing/amit-panghal-to-spearhead-indias-challenge-at-world-championships/articleshow/70144159.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amit Panghal rode on his Asian Championships gold to get a direct entry, while Commonwealth Games silver-medallist Manish Kaushik edged past Shiva Thapa in India's eight-strong squad for the World Boxing Championships in September.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70144266,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1569232,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562672726]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA["MS Dhoni's Got Virat Kohli's Back": Fans' Shirts Evoke ICC Tweet]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-ms-dhonis-got-virat-kohlis-back-fans-shirts-evokes-icc-tweet-2066768]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[A set of Indian fans at Old Trafford wore distinctive shirts that got the ICC tweeting smartly about it.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/rse5ho8_india_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562672156]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Attacks on Big Tech Likely at White House Social Media 'Summit']]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/social-networking/news/attacks-on-big-tech-likely-at-white-house-social-media-summit-2066772]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[President Donald Trump is gearing up for a fresh assault on Silicon Valley this week with a "social media summit."]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/donald_trump_reuters_1562671981188.JPG]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562672136]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Qualcomm Launches Quad-Core Snapdragon 215 SoC for Budget Smartphones]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/mobiles/news/qualcomm-snapdragon-215-soc-launch-quad-core-cortex-a53-cpu-budget-android-smartphones-2066738]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Qualcomm Snapdragon 215 SoC will be available through Android smartphones later this year.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/qualcomm_snapdragon_215_1562670135216.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562671801]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Exclusive: China's PLA signals it will keep Hong Kong-based troops in barracks]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/EzaQQ8mZdwM/exclusive-chinas-pla-signals-it-will-keep-hong-kong-based-troops-in-barracks-idINKCN1U40RB]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Chinese military commander responsible for Hong Kong has assured a Pentagon official that Chinese troops will not interfere in the city's affairs – an apparent signal that they will stay in their barracks amid renewed political upheaval.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406051455&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680HQ]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562671662]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Broadcom Said to Make Progress on Symantec Deal With Financing, Savings]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/telecom/news/broadcom-said-to-make-progress-on-symantec-deal-with-financing-savings-2066758]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Broadcom has secured financing and identified cost savings for the acquisition of Symantec, according to people familiar with the matter.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/symantec_reuters-full_1562670962879.JPG]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562671347]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[MS Dhoni's School Students Keen To Watch Him Batting In India vs New Zealand World Cup Semi-Final]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/ms-dhonis-school-students-keen-to-watch-him-batting-in-india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-2066756]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hotels in the city have made no special arrangements for the match due to a notice slapped by the BCCI.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/5bbmrto8_ms-dhoni-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562671198]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Indian team management criticised for excluding Shami]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/icc-world-cup-2019-indian-team-management-criticised-for-excluding-shami/articleshow/70143719.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Indian team management was on Tuesday criticised on social media after they did not include right-arm pacer Mohammed Shami in the playing XI for the World Cup semi-final clash against New Zealand at the Old Trafford in Manchester.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70143711,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1907763,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562671035]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semi-Final: Hat-Trick Man Mohammed Shami Not Part of India Playing XI vs New Zealand]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-mohammed-shami-not-part-of-india-playing-xi-for-semi-final-2066711]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mohammed Shami has been clinical with the ball, taking 14 wickets in just four matches in the World Cup 2019.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/n5nvef1g_mohammed-shami-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562670782]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand, Semi Final: When And Where To Watch Live Telecast, Live Streaming]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-when-and-where-to-watch-live-telecast-live-streaming-2066124]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi Final Match: All-round performances and some individual batting prowess saw India top the World Cup 2019 league stage.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/9v0cql08_india-team-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562670766]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Roger Federer Eyes 100th Wimbledon Win And Rafael Nadal Showdown]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/roger-federer-looks-to-set-up-semis-clash-against-rafael-nadal-with-eyes-on-100th-wimbledon-win-2066740]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a quarter-final line-up, there is a growing anticipation of a potential 40th career match-up between the sport's two most successful players.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/4aelbcro_roger-federer-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562670746]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Google Pulls Scam Samsung Updates App That Was Downloaded 10 Million Times]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/apps/news/google-suspends-updates-for-samsung-scam-app-that-was-downloaded-10-million-times-2066733]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Google has suspended a fraudulent mobile app on the Google Play Store called 'Updates for Samsung' for violating its policies that claimed to offer system-level Android updates to smartphones.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/Google_play_1556370733178.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562669729]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Apple's Classic Texas Hold'em Game Is Back on the App Store]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/games/news/apple-texas-holdem-game-re-released-on-the-app-store-download-2066731]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Apple has released a redesigned version of its iconic game Texas Hold'em on the App Store. The refreshed app is now available as a free download on the App Store.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/tex-mainn_1562670111278.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562669627]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Nifty, Sensex erase losses to close little changed]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/Kjk8McaHZGk/nifty-sensex-erase-losses-to-close-little-changed-idINKCN1U40EW]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indian shares recovered from earlier falls to close little changed on Tuesday, with losses in Titan Company Ltd  offset by gains in Bajaj Finance Ltd.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406012412&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680BZ]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562669608]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Federer eyes 100th Wimbledon win and Nadal showdown]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/tennis/wimbledon-2019/federer-eyes-100th-wimbledon-win-and-nadal-showdown/articleshow/70143357.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Roger Federer can rack up his 100th win at Wimbledon on Wednesday and set-up a blockbuster semi-final against Rafael Nadal.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70143352,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1568635,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562669060]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Google Stadia Games Will Remain Playable Even if Publishers Withdraw]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/games/news/google-stadia-games-wont-disappear-if-publishers-withdraw-faq-update-2066705]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Google has released additional information about how its Stadia game streaming service will launch]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/stadia_google_io_ndtv_1562669013774.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562669030]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Yuvraj Singh Regrets Not Settling In Any IPL Franchise]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/cricket/yuvraj-singh-regrets-not-settling-in-any-ipl-franchise-2066722]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yuvraj Singh played for Kings XI Punjab, Pune Warriors, Royal Challengers Bangalore, Delhi Capitals, Sunrisers Hyderabad and Mumbai Indians.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/l0n1ofv8_yuvraj-singh-bcciipl_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562668759]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Hong Kong leader says extradition bill is dead, but critics unconvinced]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/q07N0Oky-1Y/hong-kong-leader-says-extradition-bill-is-dead-but-critics-unconvinced-idINKCN1U4089]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hong Kong leader Carrie Lam said on Tuesday the extradition bill that sparked the Chinese-ruled city's biggest crisis in decades is dead and that government work on the legislation had been a "total failure", but critics accused her of playing with words.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1405981067&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF6807I]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562667407]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sanjay Manjrekar Excludes Ravindra Jadeja In Playing XI For Semi-Final, Faces Backlash On Twitter]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-sanjay-manjrekar-excludes-ravindra-jadeja-from-playing-xi-2066693]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sanjay Manjrekar and Ravindra Jadeja were involved in a spat on social media which refuses to die down.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/9d25jpv8_ravindra-jadeja-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562666782]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand World Cup Semi Final: Airspace Over Old Trafford To Remain Shut During Match, English Board Tells BCCI]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-airspace-over-old-trafford-to-remain-shut-during-match-eng-2066591]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The decision has been taken after consultation with the local authorities, the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB) has informed the BCCI.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/6u2khek8_india-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562666410]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Was never settled in any IPL franchise: Yuvraj Singh]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/news/was-never-settled-in-any-ipl-franchise-yuvraj-singh/articleshow/70142581.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yuvraj Singh played for six different franchises in the IPL. "I was never settled in whichever franchise I played for. I didn't really get settled where you are made to play for one franchise or maybe two. I probably had my best IPL season with RCB. It was unfortunate not to come to KKR," he said.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70142555,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1242479,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562666077]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sacred Games Season 2 to Release on August 15, Trailer Out]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/entertainment/news/sacred-games-2-season-release-date-august-15-netflix-india-saif-ali-khan-nawazuddin-siddiqui-2066617]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sacred Games season 2, the second part of the much-awaited show, will be back on Netflix on August 15. Netflix has also shared the Sacred Games 2 trailer.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/sacred_games_youtube_full_1562660534175.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562666053]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Nintendo Says to Shift Part of Switch Console Production Out of China]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://gadgets.ndtv.com/games/news/nintendo-switch-production-to-be-partially-shifted-out-of-china-2066689]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nintendo plans to shift part of the production of its Switch gaming console to Vietnam from China to diversify manufacturing sites.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://i.gadgets360cdn.com/large/nindendo_reuters_1562665672308.JPG]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Technology]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562665817]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Mirabai Chanu Wins Gold At Commonwealth Senior Weightlifting Championship]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/weightlifting/mirabai-chanu-wins-gold-at-commonwealth-senior-weightlifting-championship-2066686]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Indian contingent won 13 medals that included eight gold, three silver and two bronze medals in senior, junior and youth categories.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/lkacr99_mirabai-chanu-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562665735]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Mirabai Chanu wins gold at Commonwealth Championship]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/more-sports/others/mirabai-chanu-wins-gold-at-commonwealth-senior-weightlifting-championship/articleshow/70142251.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Former world champion Mirabai Chanu led the Indian medal rush by notching up a gold on the opening day of the Commonwealth Weightlifting Championship here on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70142272,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-161721,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562664969]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand World Cup 2019 Semi-final: Rohit Sharma One Of The Greatest ODI Batsmen, Says India Coach Ravi Shastri]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-rohit-sharma-one-of-the-greatest-odi-batsmen-says-india-coach-ravi-s-2066659]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semifinal Match: Rohit Sharma is in tremendous touch in World Cup 2019, having so far scored 647 runs from eight innings.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/m35sqm9g_rohit-sharma-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562663845]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019 Semi Final: Fan Frenzy Grows As India vs New Zealand Semi Final Approaches]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-fan-frenzy-grows-as-world-cup-2019-semi-final-gets-closer-2066566]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indian fans have been thronging Old Trafford in Manchester, braving the weather and the possibility of rain having an impact on the goings-on.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/0gan5lho_india-fans-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562663573]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Trump says won't deal with UK ambassador after leak of 'inept' memos]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/6aUE43ebhj4/trump-says-wont-deal-with-uk-ambassador-after-leak-of-inept-memos-idINKCN1U30PQ]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Donald Trump said he would not deal with Britain's ambassador to Washington after a leak of confidential memos in which the diplomat described the U.S. president's administration as "inept".
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s2.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406008578&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680BI]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562663297]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[U.S. State Department approves possible $2.2 billion arms sale to Taiwan]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/fZ-j1uuzQxc/u-s-state-department-approves-possible-2-2-billion-arms-sale-to-taiwan-idINKCN1U32HV]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The U.S. State Department has approved the possible sale to Taiwan of M1A2T Abrams tanks, Stinger missiles and related equipment at an estimated value of $2.2 billion, the Pentagon said on Monday, despite Chinese criticism of the deal.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406006405&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF671SM]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562661945]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Budget fiscally prudent, to help mid-term India story: Mowat]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/markets/expert-view/budget-was-fiscally-prudent-and-will-help-medium-term-india-story-adrian-mowat/articleshow/70141285.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Budget will have relatively modest near-term impacts rather than something that impacts the medium-term story for India which was actually helped by the budget because it was fiscally prudent, says Adrian Mowat, Emerging Markets equity strategist. Excerpts from interview with ETNOW.A day after a heavy selloff, there is post-budget nervousness, particularly about how the surcharge on the super rich may impact FPIs and flows into India. What is your takeaway?There are a couple of factors to look at here for the markets. We have got a global issue which is expectations around Fed cuts. We are impacted by the US employment data which was very strong; the best we have been so far in 2019. So, global markets are coming off. The budget was fiscally prudent for a government that has just won a strong mandate. The budget had little in it that would provide a short-term boost to earnings and to the market. As you look through the details -- decreasing the maximum holding promoters can have in stocks, some of the taxation issues -- then the interpretation is that there is a degree of an overhang/inability for the wealthy to invest in India in a tax-efficient way. We have had a good rally in markets, whether it be global markets or the Indian market, and we are having a degree of sell on news. I would not overplay some of these factors that came out of the budget. There are relatively modest near-term impacts rather than something that impacts the medium-term story for India; which in my view was helped by the budget because it was fiscally prudent. There is a sense of a consumption slowdown as we head into earnings. The budget provided stimulus on the monetary side which may not be transmitted and may also take a while. And, we are still waiting on the expected rate cuts. Do you feel that this is going to be enough to really get things going again or do you see a prolonged period of pain on the back of this slowdown?Well, the budget in trying to be fiscally prudent will be a drag on the economy. Now you got the Reserve Bank offsetting that, if they continue to ease. This is a sensible way of dealing with the challenges within the Indian economy. The problem for the market is that there is no incremental good news coming out of the budget. We have had a good rally in Indian equities, predominately driven by the election result which was much better than the market was expecting. That was combined with a rally in US equities which was driven by good economic data, as well as a much more dovish Fed. Perhaps, now we have gotten past that optimum point in the market where good economic data is interpreted as a less accommodative Fed. We have passed the sweet spot. Markets are probably due for a bit of correction and that is occurring at this point. Now, with regards to the Indian economy, consumption and business investment, I do not see any near-term positive drivers for consumption. The Indian consumer is not overly sensitive to interest rates. There are other factors that can be more dominant within the Indian economy. Some of the things that came out of the budget may increase the propensity of countries and global organisations to invest in factories and other services in India. In the longer term that might help consumption.What do you make of some stocks like Bajaj, Titan, etc? What will happen when these stocks start to correct?You are referring to Bajaj Finance which has been an outstanding performer year to date. Investors are looking for excuses to make some profits and you will see corrections in the stocks that have had the biggest movements. This is a normal event in capital markets. It is nothing to get overly excited by. There is probably further downside risk for these stocks as investors reduce positions. But I do not know if this tells us that there is a profound change in the case for investment in these stocks. I do not think there is. It is merely a correction in these markets.How are you viewing the financials given the rescue package that was announced for NBFCs? Do you feel that it will ease some stress in the system? Are you happy that they actually addressed it or do you feel it was just covering up for the mess that has already been made for the lower quality names?We have got a NBFC issue. We have also got a PSU bank recapitalisation issue. Analysts are interpreting it as good news in more capital being provided, but the capital also seeming to be more of a minimum requirement than a sum of money that resolves the issue for the long term. We will continue to be discussing issues with NBFCs and undercapitalised PSU banks. Now that we have had some change in regulations, particularly for housing finance companies, the market will probably treat that as a positive thing as the regulation may get more robust and homogeneous across the different types of institutions. That is probably a good long-term fundamental new story for India.Speaking about overall consumption, reports indicate that the overall rural slowdown is also likely to lead to a massive deceleration, and that recovery is going to take time. How long will the overall consumption slowdown take to recover?To change the consumption slowdown, you need to boost rural incomes. You need to do things to improve urban real incomes. What could happen here is that crop could be better than expected if the monsoon is better than expected. At the moment, the news flow about the monsoon is more on the negative side. There is no indication out of the budget that you are going to see an increase in minimum support prices or in subsidies into rural India. So, it looks like we are going to be weather dependent there. I think for urban India it is whether we get more political certainty. We have had a prudent budget with some positive measures to make FDI easier into India. But perhaps the job creation will prove more robust over the next 12 months and actually boost incomes of the household sector which allows consumption to recover. As an equity investor, the whole consumption story is very frustrating at a market cap level. Remember a huge amount of the consumer discretionary index is the auto names. With the move to electric vehicles you got a really nasty gap in the demand for automobiles for the next couple of years. What is happening globally is that individuals that own cars are keeping them for longer as they are waiting for new technology to hit the right price point, which would then generate a replacement cycle throughout capital markets. Whether it is Germany, United States, United Kingdom, or Japan. the auto sector is under extreme pressure and that is a big way that you play the consumer discretionary theme. Also, the autos will drive consumer financing. Auto financing is a big part of the finance industry beyond mortgages. I think the consumption story as you play it in capital markets is going to be quite frustrating because much of the market cap has been hit by this secular-technology story, as opposed to a cyclical up-and-down consumption. I want to get your perspective on the sentiment in the market right now. If you look at a stock like Titan, it is down about 10% at this point of time. Are most people just finding a reason to sell large cap counters where they have made money?Well, let us be careful about how we comment on these things. We are talking about a market that has done very year to date. We have had a correction on Monday and that correction is continuing today. So, before we decide that this is a medium-term trend, let us be conscious about the time frame we are talking about. We do have concerns around consumption, but it sounds to me like the Titan story is a very specific one. The stock has preformed well and expectations were about what the company can deliver. Their announcement is being treated quite sensibly as a reason to reduce your position in the stock.Do you see more flows coming in? What is your outlook when it comes to the debt side?The near-term outlook for flows is going to be quite poor. We are seeing a correction in global equities, and also a strong performance. We have had a rapid decline in bond yields for much of the year where you ended up with the funny shape in the yield curve. As the investment community pays more attention to the US economic data -- which remains very advanced and undoubtedly -- some of the most important you should ever look at in a consumption driven economy -- the outlook on higher bond yields may be a more normalised. If that is the case, then you are going to get some broader pressure on the credit markets, including emerging markets. I would be cautious on flows as we move through the summer months. It could be a very normal seasonal pattern where you get the rally being powerful in the first half of the year, then a correction during the summer months, and then as people start to think about the following calendar year(September-October), you begin to get some recovery in markets. So, do be cautious about expecting international capital flows to underpin markets. I do not think that is going to be the trend. I want to touch upon the fresh offering that we are going to see post the change in public shareholding norms that have been announced. Do you feel that the market has the appetite, not just for the some of the higher quality names like TCS, Wipro, etc, but also for the PSUs that are going to be changing that shareholding?The market has the appetite for this issuance, definitely for high-quality names. Investors would welcome a higher free float as it would increase India’s rating in the MSCI indices, which is obviously helpful in a world where there is a lot of passive products. With regards to the PSUs, it depends on the businesses. Investors are very concerned about corporate governance and would like to see independent boards that are protecting the interests of the minority investor as opposed to representing government departments. If the change in norms which results in the government hoping to raise more money through disinvestments makes them begin to understand the importance of properly restructuring PSUs, then that could be very positive for India. Unfortunately, India had the habit of allowing its public sector units to wither away, be it BSNL, MTNL, Air India, or banks. Now is the time when the government has such a strong mandate to really put through some major reforms for public sector units and make them proper private sector entities; maybe still with a big public sector passive investment. That would be the best thing for the Indian economy. It would also be the best thing for the employees of those companies. It would be much better to be in a robust well-managed entity, rather than a PSU which continues to lose market share. So, I think it is a great question and it really depends on what we are being sold. And if we are being sold a good restructuring story where there is proper reform, then I think there will be plenty of appetite. If we are being sold a minority stake in a PSU where the chairman changes every three years with no long-term strategy, then I think investors will be very cynical.What is your take on autos? Do you continue to remain underweight in your outlook on the banking space as a whole?Structurally underweight autos globally, whether they are manufacturers, a part of the supply chain, or distributors. It has to do with the transition to electric vehicles. If you recall back to when we used to have televisions which were big bulky things with cathode-ray tubes in the living rooms, we recognised that plasma TVs and TFT TVs were the new way to go. But they were far too expensive. So, what we kept our TV until eventually we could afford the flat panel TV to watch cricket on. That is happening in the auto sector. People recognise that electric vehicles are the new technology, but they do not want to commit substantial capital to replacing their vehicles. That results in this demand gap. The auto sector is structurally underweight. It may have some short-term rallies, but against this very difficult structural background and frustration in trying to get consumer exposure when such a big part of the consumer discretionary index is structurally challenged, it is a big issue for equity investors. With regard to banks, you know you have got the classic rally in India. That is a rally of high quality names, big distribution, and performance this year. So, the private sector high-quality banks have performed extremely well. We are perhaps seeing a correction based on the budget announcement of 70000 crores going into PSU banks. But I view that as a more tactical story. You are still better off staying with these high quality and high ROE private sector banks, rather than move into the PSU banks even with modest recapitalisation. So the broad story here is that the market has done well, we are getting a correction, and you are going to see a correction that will be more dramatic in the stocks that have done well. Look at the fundamentals of those and they are probably going to give an opportunity -- maybe a month or so from now -- to add back to these high quality names. ]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://img.etimg.com/thumb/width-310,resizemode-4,msid-70141285/budget-fiscally-prudent-to-help-mid-term-india-story-mowat.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Top News]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562661384]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand, World Cup Semi-Final: Saina Nehwal Leads Wishes For Team]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semifinal-saina-nehwal-leads-wishes-for-team-india-ahead-of-big-match-2066544]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the momentum grows for the World Cup 2019 semi-final between India and New Zealand, stars from other sports added their support for Team India.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/5sn1885o_india-team-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562659676]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[China calls on U.S. to withdraw arms sale to Taiwan]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/xjth8GcSDb4/china-calls-on-u-s-to-withdraw-arms-sale-to-taiwan-idINKCN1U40P9]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[China's foreign ministry called on the United States on Tuesday to withdraw a potential $2.2 billion arms sales to Taiwan, saying it strongly opposes the action.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources_v2/images/rcom-default.png]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562658483]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Virat Kohli, Kane Williamson's Mutual Admiration To Light Up World Cup Semifinal]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-virat-kohli-kane-williamsons-mutual-admiration-to-light-up-world-cup-semi-final-2066443]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semifinal: Virat Kohli pointed out how he always saw talent in Kane Williamson. The New Zealand skipper said the Indian skipper has evolved over the years and is an absolute run-machine at present.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/tefuoopg_india-vs-new-zealand-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562656216]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semifinal, India vs New Zealand: India Probable Playing XI, New Zealand Probable Playing XI]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-india-probable-playing-xi-new-zealand-probable-playing-xi-2066406]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India and New Zealand didn't play each other in the league stage as the match in Nottingham was abandoned without toss due to rain.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/tcf4aa28_ms-dhoni-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562655896]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Special Prayers In UP Before India vs New Zealand World Cup Semifinal]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/special-prayers-in-up-before-india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-2066530]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prayers are being held for the victory of the Indian team in the semi-finals.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/r774tql8_india-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562655389]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[ICC World Cup: What happens if semis or final is washed out?]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/icc-world-cup-what-happens-if-semis-or-final-is-washed-out/articleshow/70139466.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fickle English weather has made an impact on matches more than once during the 2019 ICC World Cup. Four of the 45 league matches were washed out, the most in a single edition of the ODI World Cup.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70139467,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1200941,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562653838]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rahul Dravid appointed head of cricket at NCA]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/EgY1PzApsTc/rahul-dravid-appointed-head-of-cricket-at-nca-idINKCN1U40I3]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Former India captain Rahul Dravid has been appointed Head of Cricket at the National Cricket Academy (NCA) in Bengaluru, the country's board (BCCI) said on Monday.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s3.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406017839&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680DM]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562650484]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India inflation likely rose in June, but below RBI target: Reuters poll]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INtopNews/~3/xb-sbLU6ZBg/india-inflation-likely-rose-in-june-but-below-rbi-target-reuters-poll-idINKCN1U40EO]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India's retail inflation likely reached an eight-month high in June on rising food prices, but stayed under the Reserve Bank of India's medium-term target of 4% for an eleventh straight month, a Reuters poll predicted.
  
]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://s4.reutersmedia.net/resources/r/?m=02&d=20190709&t=2&i=1406112823&w=1200&r=LYNXNPEF680SY]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Headlines]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562648933]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[No Neymar, No Problem As Brazil Begin New Copa America Reign]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/football/no-neymar-no-problem-as-brazil-begin-new-copa-america-reign-2066399]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet as this year's Copa campaign unfolded, Brazil demonstrated that it might have finally cast off the longstanding criticisms of "Neymar-dependency."]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/9sglpr7_neymar-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562643574]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Serena Williams Wary Of Alison Riske Factor At Wimbledon Quarters]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/serena-williams-wary-of-alison-riske-factor-at-wimbledon-quarters-2066392]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Serena Williams is moving into something resembling her best form after an unconvincing first week but will not take Tuesday's quarter-final opponent Alison Riske lightly.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/5528pd0o_serena-williams-afp_625x300_09_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562642647]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Grateful for what MS Dhoni has done for us, says Virat Kohli]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/sports/cricket/icc-world-cup/world-cup-2019-grateful-for-what-ms-dhoni-has-done-for-us-says-virat-kohli/articleshow/70136398.cms]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[MS Dhoni is highly unlikely to feature in the next edition of the 50-over World Cup as the wicketkeeper-batsman turned 38 on Sunday. Virat Kohli sidestepped questions on a possible send-off for the former captain as he praised the veteran's contribution to Indian cricket. Virat said giving space to players to make their own decisions was Dhoni's biggest quality.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/msid-70136401,width-1070,height-580,imgsize-1196926,resizemode-6,overlay-toi_sw,pt-32,y_pad-40/photo.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562638822]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rafael Nadal, Novak Djokovic And Roger Federer Untroubled At Wimbledon As Monday Proves Not So Manic]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/rafael-nadal-leads-charge-of-old-brigade-into-wimbledon-quarter-finals-2066330]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third seed Rafael Nadal swept to an easy 6-2, 6-2, 6-2 win over Joao Sousa of Portugal.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/p3gjpreo_rafael-nadal-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562610080]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2019: Bangladesh Sack Coach Steve Rhodes After Disappointing Campaign]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/bangladesh-sack-coach-steve-rhodes-after-lacklustre-world-cup-2019-2066339]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bangladesh Cricket Board confirmed coach Steve Rhodes will not travel with the team to Sri Lanka, where Bangladesh will play three ODIs later this month.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/73ku0ehs_bangladesh-coach-steve-rhodes-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562609375]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[I-League Clubs Urge PM To Form Panel To Probe AIFF's Functioning]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/football/i-league-clubs-urge-pm-to-form-panel-to-probe-aiffs-functioning-2066338]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Six I-League clubs have written to Prime Minister Narendra Modi, urging him to save Indian football from victimisation by the All India Football Federation (AIFF) by forming an enquiry commission.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/i32sv0s8_i-league-logo-twitter_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562609279]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Paris Saint-Germain "Regret" Neymar No-Show At Training]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/football/paris-saint-germain-regret-neymar-no-show-at-training-2066335]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neymar left Barcelona to join PSG for a world record fee of 222 million euros (USD 252 million) in August 2017, but could make a surprise move back to Camp Nou this summer.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/va0fadsc_neymar-chilling-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562607898]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA["Respect For Him Is Always Going To Be Sky High", Says Virat Kohli Praising MS Dhoni]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/virat-kohli-says-respect-for-ms-dhoni-is-always-going-to-be-sky-high-2066202]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Praising MS Dhoni, Virat Kohli said, "We are all very grateful for what MS Dhoni has done, he is always in a very happy, jovial mood".]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/ts962ulo_virat-kohli-ms-dhoni_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562604943]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[FERC revises three-year forecast to reflect rapid growth of renewable energy]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/RenewableEnergyNewsRssFeed/~3/_FF2SsHUYzM/ferc-revises-threeyear-forecast-to-reflect-rapid-growth-of-renewable-energy.html]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to a review by the SUN DAY Campaign of data just released by the Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC), within the past month, the agency has dramatically revised its three-year forecast for changes in the U.S. electrical generating capacity mix. Sharp declines are foreseen for fossil fuels and nuclear power while accompanied by even stronger growth in renewable energy (i.e., biomass, geothermal, hydropower, solar, wind) than earlier projected.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Power]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562604743]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Rahul Dravid Appointed Head Of National Cricket Academy]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/cricket/rahul-dravid-appointed-head-of-national-cricket-academy-2066320]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rahul Dravid will look after all cricket related activities at the NCA and  will be involved in mentoring, coaching, training and motivating players, coaches and the support staff at the academy.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-06/p7nfeic_rahul-dravid_625x300_29_June_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562604423]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Australia Stars Go Barefoot In World Cup Bonding Session]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/australia-stars-go-barefoot-in-world-cup-bonding-session-2066312]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The move was inspired by Australia head coach Justin Langer, who last year described himself as "a bit of a hippy", spending a month a year growing out his beard and walking barefoot.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/l9uoeu58_mitchell-starc-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562603658]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Wimbledon: Crowd-Pleasing Coco Gauff's Fairytale Run Ended By Simona Halep]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/wimbledon-2019-crowd-pleasing-coco-gauffs-fairytale-run-ended-by-simona-halep-2066307]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simona Halep, who is into Wimbledon quarter-finals for the third time, plays Zhang Shuai for a place in the last four on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/arp8vvfg_simona-halep-coco-gauff-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562602040]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Wimbledon 2019: Ashleigh Barty, Coco Gauff Exit Wimbledon As Serena Williams Coasts Through]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/tennis/wimbledon-2019-world-no-1-ashleigh-barty-knocked-out-after-losing-to-alison-riske-in-last-16-2066204]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ashleigh Barty was knocked out of Wimbledon 2019 by world number 55 Alison Riske.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/pk9j46v_ashleigh-barty-_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562601223]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semifinal: Rohit Sharma Is Tournament's "Standout Batsman", Says Kane Williamson]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-rohit-sharma-is-tournaments-standout-batsman-says-kane-wil-2066298]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India and New Zealand will battle it out for a place in World Cup 2019 final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/l9updmd8_rohit-sharma_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562599919]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[World Cup Semifinal, India vs New Zealand: New Zealand Can Upset India If They Start Well, Says Daniel Vettori]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/world-cup-semi-final-new-zealand-can-upset-india-if-they-start-well-says-daniel-vettori-2066282]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[New Zealand head into the World Cup semifinal match after losing three consecutive games against Pakistan, Australia and England.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/vr8dov3_new-zealand_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562596265]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Natural Gas beat coal in the US. Will renewables and storage beat gas?]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/RenewableEnergyNewsRssFeed/~3/YVqBp8hrdAw/natural-gas-beat-coal-in-the-us-will-renewables-and-storage-beat-gas.html]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In April 2019, in the heart of coal country, Indiana regulators rejected a proposal by its electric and gas utility, Vectren, to replace baseload coal plants with a new $900 million, 850 megawatt (MW) natural gas-fired power plant. Regulators were concerned that with the dramatic decline in the cost of renewable energy, maturation of energy storage and rapidly changing customer demand, such a major gas plant investment could become a stranded, uneconomic asset in the future. Regulators are now pushing Vectren to consider more decentralized, lower-carbon resources such as wind, solar and storage that would offer greater resource diversity, flexibility and cost effectiveness.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Power]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562590800]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand, World Cup Semi-Final: India's Road To Semi-Final]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-indias-road-to-semi-final-2066226]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[The next hurdle ahead of India in their World Cup 2019 campaign is New Zealand, runners-up from the last edition, who would want to make it to their second successive final.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/vf823jeg_india-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562590314]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi-Final: Virat Kohli, Kane Williamson 2008 U-19 World Cup Rivalry Revived]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-virat-kohli-kane-williamson-2008-u-19-world-cup-rivalry-revived-2066106]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Virat Kohli and Kane Williamson will face off on a big stage, 11 years after the 2009 U-19 World Cup semi-final where two had led their respective sides.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/avith258_kane-williamson-_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562588499]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Virat Kohli Happy To Alter His Role On Account Of Rohit Sharma's Red-Hot Form]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/virat-kohli-happy-to-alter-his-role-on-account-of-rohit-sharmas-red-hot-form-2066183]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma has smashed a record five centuries in a single World Cup to lead the tournament batting charts with 647 runs from eight innings.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/duknkae4_virat-kohli-rohit-sharma-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562588370]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand, Semi-Final: New Zealand's Road To Semi-Finals]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-new-zealands-road-to-semi-finals-2066192]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi Final Match: New Zealand's positive net run rate worked in their favour as they secured fourth spot on the points table.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/90k9kqi_new-zealand-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562587113]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA["I'm Quite Lethal": Virat Kohli Makes Light Of His Bowling Skills Ahead Of India vs New Zealand Semi-Final]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/virat-kohli-makes-light-of-his-bowling-skills-ahead-of-india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-2066171]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Virat Kohli is leading India into the World Cup 2019 first semi-final against New Zealand, to be played in Manchester on Tuesday.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/6dvkke44_virat-kohli-presser-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562585639]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Hanergy to deliver 400 MW of solar to Democratic Republic of Congo]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/RenewableEnergyNewsRssFeed/~3/APdx3nN5Tzo/hanergy-to-deliver-400-mw-of-solar-to-democratic-republic-of-congo.html]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese solar company Hanergy Thin Film Power Group has won a deal to build the first solar PV plants in the Democratic Republic of Congo.]]></description>
      <category><![CDATA[Power]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562580960]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand, World Cup Semi-Final: Face-Off, Jasprit Bumrah vs Kane Williamson]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-face-off-jasprit-bumrah-vs-kane-williamson-2066093]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Jasprit Bumrah and Kane Williamson, the World Cup 2019 first semi-finals possibly sees two of the most important players who can change the fortunes of their teams.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/fr5ujdu_jasprit-bumrah_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562579906]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Happy Birthday Sourav Ganguly: "Dada" Turns 47, Wishes Pour In]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/cricket/happy-birthday-sourav-ganguly-dada-turns-47-wishes-pour-in-2066087]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sourav Ganguly led India to World Cup 2003 final and inculcated an aggressive approach to the game that helped India claim great heights.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/j25m0oq8_sourav-ganguly-twitter_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562579750]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand, World Cup Semi-Final: Face-Off, Virat Kohli vs Lockie Ferguson]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-world-cup-semi-final-face-off-virat-kohli-vs-lockie-ferguson-2066068]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unless injury keeps Lockie Ferguson out, he will be deployed to fire his howitzers at the Indian batting, with Virat Kohli in the key No. 3 position to counter the assault.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/rms188lg_virat-kohli_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562577979]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi Final: Face-Off, Rohit Sharma vs Trent Boult]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-face-off-rohit-sharma-vs-trent-boult-2066022]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi Final Match: Rohit Sharma has had a phenomenal World Cup 2019 and his form promises more. However, New Zealand's ace left-arm seamer Trent Boult may not agree.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/kjftn2c8_rohit-sharma-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562574976]]></pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi-Final: Face-Off, Yuzvendra Chahal vs Ross Taylor]]></title>
      <link><![CDATA[https://sports.ndtv.com/world-cup-2019/india-vs-new-zealand-semi-final-face-off-yuzvendra-chahal-vs-ross-taylor-2066039]]></link>
      <description><![CDATA[India vs New Zealand Semi Final Match: While the Indian fast bowlers have been reaping rewards, how the Indian spinners fare in the first semi-final could well be crucial.]]></description>
      <image>
        <url><![CDATA[https://c.ndtvimg.com/2019-07/7cfc7gko_yuzvendra-chahal-afp_625x300_08_July_19.jpg]]></url>
      </image>
      <category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
      <pubDate><![CDATA[1562574853]]></pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
